100xEngineers: Hey, hi folks, how you doing?
100xEngineers: Hey guys, let me… let me know in the chat, how are you guys feeling?
100xEngineers: We have a very interesting session, by the way, today.
100xEngineers: So I'm feeling, on a scale of…
100xEngineers: 1 to 10, I think, somewhere around…
100xEngineers: 9.5, actually. Yeah. I was preparing for this.
100xEngineers: And, usually, usually I do this session as a… as a final sprint.
100xEngineers: Because every lecture when we take, I try to keep it first principle heavy, theory heavy, and sometimes, like, Socratic, so I ask questions, but sometimes we need those freestyle lectures or sessions where you can see the raw building part and the raw life thinking part. This is one of those kind of sessions.
100xEngineers: I won't be doing the usual Q&A, including the first principle thinking. In fact, like, we won't be learning a lot of new things today. The lecture today is about
100xEngineers: building something, and that's the goal. So, just to set the agenda, it's gonna be, as I said, in the title, Live MVP Build and Deploy. The idea and the goal of this lecture
100xEngineers: In the next… 120 minutes.
100xEngineers: We will go from an idea to… And full-fledged application.
100xEngineers: I won't use any old code, I won't also use the repository which we've been working towards. We'll start everything fresh, so even if you are somebody who has maybe not watched the previous lectures, not attended the previous assignments yet, this could be a point where you can just
100xEngineers: watch me and, like, do everything. By the end of it, I'll share the post-read notes with all the timestamps, so that anybody wants to follow along, so this can become, like, one of those lectures which you can refer back when you want to go from idea to app, and, based on every single thing that we have learned. So that's the agenda, that's the goal.
100xEngineers: Yes, you can do that. I'll tell more about the hackathon. We'll start the hackathon tonight, but I'll discuss more about the problem statements and everything, and the rules of it after the lecture. And this also, like, marks a…
100xEngineers: a good point to take this lecture, because I want to first show you, this is kind of my mini hackathon, which I'm doing in front of you live. So, I have already chosen a problem statement, I'll try to, like, build it live.
100xEngineers: And maybe, like, this gives a good proof point to everyone that things are possible. Now, I also want to, like, put a disclaimer out, that because I'll be building things live, and I'm not perfect, so I can make mistakes, I'll be using AI, AI can make mistakes. So things can go on the other side as well.
100xEngineers: Just bear with me, like, if basically we are trying to do debugging. But the goal is to actually show you that, like, things break in production, things break while you're building, but how do we navigate those situations, and how do we actually end up with something
100xEngineers: Like, useful at the end of the session, so that's… that's the goal.
100xEngineers: Do you follow along or just watch? Right now, I won't recommend to follow along, unless until you are very clear with all the concepts. If you are somebody who already knows these things very well, you have tried already building something, then definitely, but unless until you have done that, I won't recommend to follow along. Maybe you can follow along post the lecture.
100xEngineers: Awesome.
100xEngineers: So… Let me first…
100xEngineers: share the screen, and I'll set the context of what is the idea and what we are building.
100xEngineers: The app is gonna be same, because I don't want to…
100xEngineers: I mean, say, the observation and the idea is gonna be same. I don't want people to learn about new context, so that everybody knows. This is the same hypothesis which we have discussed. The hypothesis which I had, and this is the problem statement which I'm trying to solve.
100xEngineers: Right now, as well.
100xEngineers: that I believe… ambitious career professionals. Not only early, but… I'll make one change here.
100xEngineers: All the ambitious professionals in…
100xEngineers: Urban India. Right now, that's my specific target, but it's generally true across the world. Who are AI-aware but have no shift proof are stuck because they lack a method to convert broad AI possibility into one specific scoped workflow worth solving. And if you provide a structured workflow diagnosis system.
100xEngineers: followed by a guided build sprint, then at least 60% of proactive students will identify one real user, map one repeated workflow, build a working AI-assisted version.
100xEngineers: That's the goal, and that's also something which I'll share, like, what we are doing and what is the progress on this so far. But today, I'll take this as my hypothesis, and we'll start
100xEngineers: with the… First, identifying the inputs and outputs. That's the core…
100xEngineers: system design process which we started. Like, first, getting what to build, and then how to build.
100xEngineers: Now, I'm taking a hypothesis which I've already tested. So, anyone who is following along, I would want you to actually test this hypothesis, whatever you're building. So, we have the discovery to MVP skill, which I've shared in the week one.
100xEngineers: We can go and you can do that. And once you have an MVP plan which you validated already, then compare this part of designing the system. And first thing, we need to do input and output.
100xEngineers: We had a story, which we've been continuously using in these lectures throughout. So the story was about
100xEngineers: RF, and I'll also keep my document open. So these are things which I genuinely do whenever I'm trying to build a problem statement, so I'm trying to also think out loud,
100xEngineers: This was the RS discovery document, where we have the observations, and we build the hypothesis, and the MVP plan, which I have to conduct, and once you do this thing, and both of these things doesn't require you to build software, by the way, this is the output of the discovery to MVP skill. The goal is to
100xEngineers: validate the problem statement even before you start building anything out of it. So this is a prerequisite of this session. Now, I'll come to the inputs and output. Now, one thing which will help me to do the inputs and output here is, because I have done this experiment.
100xEngineers: And I also ran this MVP, live with real…
100xEngineers: human beings. So I know that the problem my students face today is that how can they find a useful workflow? One of the inputs which we can take is
100xEngineers: somebody explained their workflow, repeated task, and the output which we can do is the exact plan to identify those repeatable patterns. So, the example which we discussed in one of those lectures was this, like, hey, I opened Jira.
100xEngineers: to check my weekly to-dos, and then I'll check high priority tasks, and I'll pick one, and create a report, and send it to my manager on Slack. So…
100xEngineers: This and the output should be, like, a plan, that what all things this person can automate.
100xEngineers: And then after that, maybe we can do a manual guided sprint, and once you do a manual guided sprint, then you can also, like, maybe automate some part of those sprints, at least the facilitation part. That becomes a veto of it, but I'll start with, like, the MVP, which can take the input as the workflow from the user.
100xEngineers: And then give the plan as an output. And whatever system which we need.
100xEngineers: in order for us to build that, we'll… we'll build along with it. So, at the end of the day.
100xEngineers: We'll have a one front-end.
100xEngineers: This can talk to our backend, which is connected to our LLM, having everything on data storage.
100xEngineers: We'll also add one more thing, which I'm not yet
100xEngineers: taught you guys as a lecture, but I'll also supplement that with resources and the text material post the lecture, so that you can follow along in a detailed manner. We'll add the login and authentication module on top of it, so that
100xEngineers: it's not only applicable for one single user, but multiple users can use it, while keeping everything secure and private. So, that's the goal, and…
100xEngineers: Now we have the input and output. Now, first thing which I would be doing is, as I said, like, first.
100xEngineers: Mapping this system.
100xEngineers: what is the input here? Is my user's…
100xEngineers: workflow description.
100xEngineers: And the output gonna be… which is gonna come from the entire system using the LLM, and the backend is gonna be a plan.
100xEngineers: So this is gonna be the plan, which is the output.
100xEngineers: When I was teaching you guys, we had started everything from a UI-first approach, which works well for when you're doing everything first time.
100xEngineers: But right now, I'm assuming all of you at least have some clarity of these things.
100xEngineers: The next time, whenever you build the application, one of the fastest way, and the more focused way, which I do, again, slightly opinionated way, but everyone can start from any part, I always start from that one particular function, which can take this input and generate this output.
100xEngineers: So my goal is not to build
100xEngineers: Any kind of software immediately, but just to write one simple function.
100xEngineers: And if you remember, like, in Python, we did that, where we had, let's say, this
100xEngineers: diagnose function. Because essentially what we are doing is we are diagnosing
100xEngineers: the workflow from what user describes. So we take the input Which becomes, here, the user's… Workflow description.
100xEngineers: And this diagnose function, because I'm gonna use Python, will return
100xEngineers: One output. And this output is gonna be the plan.
100xEngineers: So essentially, this is how I'd like to think, and most of the time, this is also the thought process. The moment I get clarity about the inputs and output.
100xEngineers: Start with the function.
100xEngineers: Not about UI, API, database, or 10 other things, just one function. Now my focus goes into this function, like, how can I take this user's workflow and generate this output?
100xEngineers: So, what I need is, first.
100xEngineers: I need to fill in the process here. So this is the P part, if you remember, the input-output process. This is the output, and the process here, I need to… I need to define, and this is also one of the
100xEngineers: Part, which is the system thinking, and the core architecture thinking, what people call
100xEngineers: is how do you convert this input into output? Now, if you have followed along in my previous lectures, you know.
100xEngineers: In this example, it's pretty straightforward.
100xEngineers: we have multiple options. One, either we can just take the workflow from a natural language, and then we can put it into a large language model, and then
100xEngineers: make this large language model call with a system instruction, so that it understands what it's supposed to do, which is, based on the input, identify the plan. And most of the language models can do that. So, in this case, my process becomes, I'll take this…
100xEngineers: input, and I'll pass it to the LLM call, and then the LLM can
100xEngineers: give me the output of this plan, and then I'll send this plan back.
100xEngineers: Although it sounds very simple, but we need to give one more thing to LM, which is the context.
100xEngineers: So, one of the core part of the next couple of weeks, we'll be learning about this only, but this is also the beginning of
100xEngineers: are… probabilistic and deterministic system design together, where I'm… I'm trying to, like, build this
100xEngineers: whole system, which has both the LLM, which is the probabilistic system, as well as the deterministic part, which is the Python system that we are building. So one of the core thing here is.
100xEngineers: how does LLM get to know that
100xEngineers: what is the good output plan? A very important thing, because not everybody has
100xEngineers: This understanding of what is a good plan looks like, especially in this case.
100xEngineers: So, one thing for us is to define what good looks like.
100xEngineers: So that I don't want to send any AI slop to RO. So we have… now, this actually…
100xEngineers: pushes us towards learning more about evals, which is a whole different chapter in our curriculum, but
100xEngineers: it's something which I want you guys to, like, start thinking from day one, not when I will teach you a particular concept. Because eval-based design or eval-first thinking is one of those… those things which will help you to, again, understand, like, how these… these things work. One of the easiest ways how I teach eval design is by writing the
100xEngineers: I think I discussed this with this
100xEngineers: This is called golden input-output pair, which means that
100xEngineers: Okay, now we have discussed this function.
100xEngineers: what is the ideal input and the ideal output requires? And let's say the ideal input may be what we've already discussed.
100xEngineers: Something like this.
100xEngineers: that, hey.
100xEngineers: So this is our idle input, and this is the idle output. Now, definitely, I have not written it properly, but in your case, because I'm trying to, like, do a sprint right now, in your case, try to, like, add as many input-output pair, which is in your
100xEngineers: language, or in your, I would say, condition, are ideal. Now, what this helps you to do is, it helps us to understand
100xEngineers: What is a good quality output looks like?
100xEngineers: Now, one more thing which helps here is.
100xEngineers: Also, looking at a bad quality output, which means an output that you won't qualify as something which is
100xEngineers: which is worth sending to RFBAC. Like, if a user comes and they are confused, we don't want to send them something which is really technical, which is beyond the scope of what they can do, or something which, again, might not make sense to them.
100xEngineers: So that are some of the things which I'll be checking manually. Now, the reason why I'm sharing this example specifically is because
100xEngineers: it forces you to take a pause before you start writing or building code, because the moment you start going into the code bit, all of these things becomes slightly, I would say, the second thought of whatever you're writing.
100xEngineers: This also helps you to, like, design the architecture, design everything on the whiteboard first, and I would also recommend you guys to, like, start with at least the approach of understanding what is the input-output, writing the function, writing the process.
100xEngineers: Writing what good looks like for your outputs, what are the golden input-output pair, which means the ideal input and ideal outputs, and what
100xEngineers: are also not the good outputs. And when you have this clarity, this will help you to write what good looks like, which is your eval system, and this is one of the core part of working with any kind of probabilistic systems, because
100xEngineers: Unlike deterministic, which is basically just a Python function, I know that this Python function, if I'm giving it an input, and let's say it's supposed to add two numbers, and that's the only thing which I have written as a logic, it'll always give me a submission of two numbers. It won't give me anything apart from that.
100xEngineers: It can't multiply by itself, it doesn't have the imagination, but LLMs can do things which are beyond the scope of what
100xEngineers: you have defined, right? And that flexibility is both a double-edged squad, and it comes with that responsibility of me understanding what is a good output looks like, and then we converting it into the eval.
100xEngineers: Now, this is all the thinking part, which I will do, and I'll also, like, think about when somebody's doing it.
100xEngineers: right after this, I… once I have a clarity, okay, this is a good plan, looks like, and
100xEngineers: maybe, like, you can embed this from day one in your codebase, or maybe you can write it still manually, because there are some places where writing evals and explicit eval is not as easy. So I would say, like, in the MVP approach, at least.
100xEngineers: Start with… Your own understanding, maybe you keep it in your head or keep it in a notebook?
100xEngineers: But do think about this before even you start building your first function. If you can, then that's great to add directly this in the codebase. One other way how I already shared, I think, this particular repository
100xEngineers: This is the, where I have all my prompts. So I was discussing this. This is a very good example of
100xEngineers: Writing down your evals.
100xEngineers: So this is one of the evals of…
100xEngineers: scoring the marketing copy based on Mr. Ogilvy's principles.
100xEngineers: Maybe something like this, if you can think about…
100xEngineers: this is what Mr. Gilvi thinks, like, what makes a copy good? And he has mentioned it into different parameters. And what we can do is we can take these parameters and convert it into, a whole
100xEngineers: output where it can score, just like how I asked you guys to score the Y. It can score each and everything based on that mark, and this actually becomes how most initial research on evaluation started. Understanding it, and then writing it down.
100xEngineers: Hmm.
100xEngineers: My screen share is paused here. Okay, let me…
100xEngineers: Sorry guys, let me just reshare my screen.
100xEngineers: Is it better?
100xEngineers: Let me also check the sound… Okay, awesome, cool, thanks.
100xEngineers: Sorry for that, I'll keep the chat open.
100xEngineers: The eval… actually, I didn't share any evals yet, but I'll… I'll come back to it. For now, let's…
100xEngineers: move to the building part, because we first need to finish the function that helps us to convert input into output. Then we'll write the plan, the process, and one of the easiest things what I can do here right now, is
100xEngineers: is create that function immediately. Which definitely will help us, and it's something which we actually did, so…
100xEngineers: Let me open my environment. And now, for the environment setup, I'll be using cloud code.
100xEngineers: to write the code, and I'll be using…
100xEngineers: GitHub right now to make sure that whatever I'm writing, I'll push it back. So, the way how I start this project is gonna be a fresh project. So I'll open my GitHub, I'll go to this…
100xEngineers: When you log into GitHub, You can click on the plus icon.
100xEngineers: new repository. So this is the fresh project we'll start.
100xEngineers: I'll mention this workflow diagnosis.
100xEngineers: tool.
100xEngineers: And right now, I'll just, like, create the repository. I'll keep it public, so that everybody can access and follow along on this repository.
100xEngineers: Now, the reason why I'm starting with GitHub repository, because it's easier for me to now keep a track of all my changes. So the first thing which I need, if you're new to GitHub.
100xEngineers: We have already shared the GitHub resources, but the easiest way for you to get started is you can…
100xEngineers: Copy this command.
100xEngineers: And you can go to your Cloud Code. So if you haven't installed Cloud Code, then you can do that, from Clot Code's website.
100xEngineers: So, the way how I download Cloud Code is…
100xEngineers: You can directly click on the button based on the machine you are… you're using, and
100xEngineers: As of now, Cloud Code is included in the pro plan, but if anybody wants to use open source model, I've also shared a guide, how can you do that? One of the easiest ways for you to is you can use something like Open Router or OLAMA. These are the two options which I shared last time.
100xEngineers: So, open router is one, another one is Olama. If you don't want to go ahead with the paid plans of
100xEngineers: Anthropic. This allows you to run everything on Cloud Code.
100xEngineers: But without,
100xEngineers: Using the paid models. So this is the command, how do you install the cloud code, Olama LaunchCloud, and this is a specific one. If you want to use Kimik 2.5, you can run it from your own local machine.
100xEngineers: Now, not everybody might have the stronger local machine, so for those people, you can fall back to open router, and this is where you can find, like, multiple models.
100xEngineers: This is all part of a sheet, so right now, I won't focus on exactly setting it up. If you want help in setup, you can refer to the tutorial, the return tutorial, which I've already uploaded. But I'll come back and,
100xEngineers: The assumption is that
100xEngineers: somebody who's following it, you have downloaded the cloud code, and you have a model, whether it's anthropic or whether it is
100xEngineers: Open source, the process will remain the exact same.
100xEngineers: Once I have a cloud code, this is my development environment setup. I might use something more, this is just to see my code base, because I don't like to refer everything on terminal, especially when I'm reviewing stuff. So, this is optional.
100xEngineers: cursor, which is the tool that I use to look at the code. So, 3 tools, I'll be using this for now.
100xEngineers: Fahim, as I said, you don't need to follow along right now. This lecture is more like a sprint, me doing a freestyle live building thing. So if I wait for everybody to follow along, then I won't be able to finish everything. So the ideal recommendation is, if you have all the concepts and all the things installed, then you can follow along. But,
100xEngineers: Yeah, if not, then maybe you can take notes right now, and then post the lecture, you can follow along with these things.
100xEngineers: Okay, now I'll go back to my cloud, and let me start a fresh session. So one thing which I discussed with, I think,
100xEngineers: You guys.
100xEngineers: Let me start a fresh session.
100xEngineers: And also put it… Here.
100xEngineers: So, after installing Claude, Right now, I'm gonna skip the permission, and claude is asking that.
100xEngineers: Do you trust that Claude can take over this folder? And I'll say yes.
100xEngineers: So… This is my cloud code setup. What I'll be doing as a first step
100xEngineers: which I also covered in the Claude workshop, that I'll be setting up my Claude.md. And I'll just ask Claude to…
100xEngineers: create a claw.md.
100xEngineers: But this MD file should live in a project. Now, because I have created a project already on GitHub.
100xEngineers: This is the one.
100xEngineers: Which we just created. So first, I'll…
100xEngineers: take a clone, which means I'll copy this project. Essentially, it's an empty project right now, but I'll still copy it, because everything which I'll be doing on my local machine, so that I can then push it back to the GitHub.
100xEngineers: So, first I'll ask Claude, clone this…
100xEngineers: repository, and I'll mention the same URL.
100xEngineers: And then… Create… the claud.md file.
100xEngineers: But…
100xEngineers: instruction.
100xEngineers: So the instruction which I'm gonna write here is also available on my GitHub.
100xEngineers: So this is the cloud instruction.
100xEngineers: Now, the Claude instruction here specifically forces Claude
100xEngineers: to do a plan and review, and work under the plan and review mode, which actually helpful for me, because if I don't do this, it becomes slightly harder for me to keep a track of
100xEngineers: what all tasks are pending, and I have to rely on Claude's memory. So sometimes, like, if I'm maybe turning off my system and then coming back.
100xEngineers: I know that all the things are documented.
100xEngineers: Another important feature, or you can say the benefit of this approach is, when you're migrating from one technology to another technology, because this is a part of what spec-driven development looks like.
100xEngineers: as we have all the documented changes that we have made to build this project in a natural language, it's easier for us to port this project into some of the technology. If today we are using Python, tomorrow, because we have specification, we can ask Claude to refer to the same specification and translate this code into different languages.
100xEngineers: Which becomes much more easier.
100xEngineers: So right now, what I did is I asked it to clone, and the repository has been cloned, and it has also created the claw.md file right now.
100xEngineers: So let me first just confirm it on my terminal as well, that do we have the depository? So I…
100xEngineers: I think I can see that this is C7 Workflow Diagnosis Tool, so I can see it is already there.
100xEngineers: Now, let me just go into this folder, so I'll… Do the change directory, and…
100xEngineers: I would close this session.
100xEngineers: Because my repository is there. And within this folder, which Claude has just cloned for me from GitHub.
100xEngineers: I'll start my Cloud session once again.
100xEngineers: Okay, so now, first thing here, as I said, I'll take an approach of Putting things on my screen.
100xEngineers: first thing which I need is a Python file. And to be honest, this entire thing, I can do it with the… without using Claude as well. So, just to give you a picture, what I'll do is maybe create
100xEngineers: a file myself.
100xEngineers: So that it'll be easier.
100xEngineers: to then visualize that what we have started with. Although it's an empty project right now, but we'll go to…
100xEngineers: 300X, let me open…
100xEngineers: So this is my cursor, and let me open… the projects… this one.
100xEngineers: And…
100xEngineers: So this also gives you a good view of what is actually there.
100xEngineers: something which I prefer a lot, rather than trusting everything that Claude is writing, I like to review everything, what it is doing. So tomorrow, if anything breaks, I have at least understanding of how can I fix those things.
100xEngineers: So as I said, like, first step for me was mapping this Python function, which I did. So what I need is I need a Python file, which I can write
100xEngineers: Very simple.
100xEngineers: To begin with, something which we started in the… API lecture.
100xEngineers: I'll call this file, let's say, main.py, because this is gonna be my main Python file where I'll mention the core business logic. And the business logic is going to be one diagnose function right now.
100xEngineers: It takes some input, and it returns
100xEngineers: the… plan.
100xEngineers: Now, the reason why I'm doing all of this, although I could have asked Claude to do this part for me, is because
100xEngineers: now I'll be, like, controlling exactly what I want.
100xEngineers: I know the process for this
100xEngineers: So, I'll write the process down, and I want to map it. I don't want to, like, first brainstorm a few things with the LLM. I know exactly the process is gonna be.
100xEngineers: It'll take the workflow description.
100xEngineers: 2LM, and 2… get the plan.
100xEngineers: Now, one major choice…
100xEngineers: Something which we have not discussed on the whiteboard yet, and this is… this is where
100xEngineers: I again believe it's important for us to understand the whole system design.
100xEngineers: If you go with any default Claude prompt, or the codex prompt, you can actually
100xEngineers: ask it, and based on whatever Claude thinks.
100xEngineers: This is the case where you'll see the bias.
100xEngineers: if you write this prompt that, hey, can you build a diagnose function, and you can take this workflow description, give it a plan, Claude will automatically think that you want to use Claude models for it.
100xEngineers: Even though Claude models are expensive, but because we are using Claude to write this
100xEngineers: program, it will fall back to the model which it has. That is a bias coming from the cloud. If you're using from GPT or Codex, then same goes with that. And that's a bias which is built in with a lot of these proprietary models. Something which I don't want to use right now, because I don't want to pay extra, to just get the plan, and I know the plan can be gathered from an open source model. So this is where the understanding
100xEngineers: comes in, and which is where I'm using my own intelligence to understand, that, hey, LLM can be
100xEngineers: for this particular part, the specific LLM
100xEngineers: like, Sonnet or Opus doesn't matter. What matters is that a system that can take the input and give us the plan, which would look good based on our
100xEngineers: Metrics.
100xEngineers: So, one other thing which I'll do is I'll try to find the open source models first. They are…
100xEngineers: multiple ways to get open source models, especially the inference, which means that you can call these models which are sitting somewhere, so you don't need to install locally everything. Although, if you have a machine, you can do that with Olama, but right now, I don't want to…
100xEngineers: put a load on my ramp. So I'll use something which is already deployed.
100xEngineers: on Grok Cloud. The reason why I'm using this platform, it's because Grok is one of the fastest inference for large language models. These guys have built a chip, which is…
100xEngineers: only focus on processing and deploying the language model, hence it, they are the fastest one. Another thing which I'm using is also free of cost. So, they have a rate limit option, which means if you go to their Grok pricing.
100xEngineers: You can find that… It has this,
100xEngineers: request per day and tokens per minute limit, which means if you're using something like Llama 3.1 instant model, it limits it to 30 requests per minute, which is…
100xEngineers: a good measure for me if I'm testing the application, and even if I'm, let's say, doing the… or building this as a workflow which is gonna be run for me, and every minute, I don't want to make more than 30 requests to a particular language model. If that is my case.
100xEngineers: I can… And basically, like, all of this, like, comes down to, let's say,
100xEngineers: Yeah, what I was saying is that all of this, let's say, comes down to under 30 requests per day. I can keep running my app for free. So there are a lot of applications which I started using and building within my workflow that
100xEngineers: That's something I use, but I don't pay for the LLM cost, because I can… I can make sure that those apps do not cross this request per minute, and then, total requests per day. So, request per day is this 14,400, and requests per minute is 30. If I…
100xEngineers: can keep my LM usage under this, I'm kind of, like, operating, you know, under a free boundary for my own personal use. Now, this is something which is interesting because
100xEngineers: by default, everybody thinks that you have to pay for LM for each and everything, and the interesting part is with open source and with Croc.
100xEngineers: If you can…
100xEngineers: keep the bottleneck low. A lot of personal workflows you can automate for free, almost. Now, in this case.
100xEngineers: as I said, maybe I might need to increase this, maybe I need to put my cart, if I'm trying to scale this for, let's say, 200, 300 people, and they all are using at the same time. But for a single user like Araf, or maybe, like, 2 users as well.
100xEngineers: I think I can still at least get started with the free model, and that's another reason why I'm using CrocCloud, so it doesn't create any bottleneck or friction for me. Now, I'll choose a model. I'll go with the Llama right now, but you can feel free to choose any other model as well in the open source ecosystem. And the way how I'll use this platform is I'll go to the API key, I'll click on the Create New API key, I'll also create a new API key.
100xEngineers: specifically for this part. So, workflow… Diagnosis… Although I'll…
100xEngineers: keep it on other window, so I won't reveal my API key.
100xEngineers: Another reminder that Don't reveal your API keys on any public platform.
100xEngineers: Okay, now I have the API key, so first let me store it somewhere.
100xEngineers: Okay, now I… I'm done with my LLM setup, so I have ALM. This is the API key which I just created. You will also be able to do this for free, you don't need to, like, pay anything to Grok, or as I said, like, under the free… under the free limit.
100xEngineers: And this helps us to, like, set up the LLM provider. Now we have the exact LLM that you want to connect, and we also know that we can build the entire MVP with almost zero cost, at least for the first MVP, or the first user. And now I'll go back with my…
100xEngineers: prompt. This is where I'll come. And I'll mention that the LM which I'm gonna use here is gonna be the Grok.
100xEngineers: Cloud.
100xEngineers: Llama… 3.1…
100xEngineers: Actually, let me just pick the exact name, so I'll go back here, I'll get the llama…
100xEngineers: Let me use the… 3.18 billion.
100xEngineers: Okay, now I have my function ready. The second thing which I need is definitely I need to expose the API key, that is how I'm gonna connect the Grok account, which I created, so that Grok knows that I'm not
100xEngineers: I would say, crossing the threshold of 30 requests per limit.
100xEngineers: So for that, I'll… the key which I created here, I need to copy it and paste it in my terminal. So there are two ways to expose an API key to any Python program.
100xEngineers: you can just write export command, so this is the command, let's say export, and grok API key.
100xEngineers: And you just paste your API key here. Now, what this does is it…
100xEngineers: export that API key in your current session, and you need to write this command, not here, but…
100xEngineers: in that terminal. So this terminal could be from the cursor terminal, where the cursor is running. So you can open the terminal from here, or you can click on this terminal section opener, and then you can, like, do this. Or you can create another terminal on a different window and just write the same command export clock API key, and paste that thing.
100xEngineers: And then you can use it from the operating system process that is running right now. The only limitation for this part is that the moment you
100xEngineers: let's say restart your PC, you again need to export it again, again. So the other better way of doing it, you create a .env file. So this is what I also prefer to do for especially bigger projects where I have multiple environment files.
100xEngineers: The .env is a very specific format. Dot means that it's hidden right now, and ENV is…
100xEngineers: for my environment variables, and I will… I won't be sharing this particular file to my GitHub repository, because I don't want to make it public.
100xEngineers: So, I'll basically write the things here, but not while I'm sharing screen. So just make sure you can write the same thing. Here, you don't need to write the export command, you can just use the Grok underscore API key, and then you can paste the API key here.
100xEngineers: This is all you need to do in order for you to, like, get started with At least…
100xEngineers: I would say a boilerplate for your function, which you have written, you have the full control of the input and output plan, and now I'll go back to the cloud, because that is where I feel like
100xEngineers: Again, this is a personal bias, because At least I have…
100xEngineers: started my whole engine, started my journey with, like, what I want.
100xEngineers: And if I go back to Claude right now, and giving Claude access to all the things which I have created, which is just a main.pui file.
100xEngineers: and a cloud.md, which tells it to do it in plan and review mode. And then the environment variable, where I've added this, Grok environment API key. Actually, let me do that.
100xEngineers: So…
100xEngineers: Okay, so now I have everything here.
100xEngineers: what I'll do is, I'll tell my client that, hey.
100xEngineers: Help me… build the… Diagnose function… And connect.
100xEngineers: the specified… At the limb.
100xEngineers: 2… Generate the plan.
100xEngineers: I'll also mention that, Actually, let me just mention that right now. The input… to this function.
100xEngineers: Now, there's something which is slightly under the gray area. Sometimes I define it with comments in Python file, sometimes I also put it in the prompt here. These days, because I'm talking to Claude a lot, hence I'm falling back to this approach, but I would recommend you guys to
100xEngineers: Like, add as many details as you can.
100xEngineers: in the Python file itself, even if you don't know the syntax, just write the comments for it, which means that the English comments in the Python file, that what you need to do. In this case, the… the input which I need to tell to Claude that what functions take, in this case is the workflow description.
100xEngineers: of my student.
100xEngineers: Say who is in… Analyst… And once… 2… Start…
100xEngineers: automation.
100xEngineers: Or… Hmm.
100xEngineers: the output… of this function.
100xEngineers: Is… A diagnosis plan, which…
100xEngineers: student can… Follow and, build the first.
100xEngineers: automation.
100xEngineers: So just a quick context to Claude. At this point, Claude has… A file, the main.py file.
100xEngineers: And, the instructions of how we should operate Claude, which is in a plan and review. And, the large language model.
100xEngineers: Which is, we have specified the Grog Cloud.
100xEngineers: Especially the Lama 3.1, and also a key, so that it can connect to that Llama 3.1 independent parameter model. So it has basically everything, and let me do it live and see if…
100xEngineers: Okay, everything is clear now. There's an API key, and python. So, it automatically installed this Python.env package, so that it can access that key. Now, this is also a smarter approach. Most people
100xEngineers: do this, where… when they are building with cloud code, and this is, by the way, not the safe practice.
100xEngineers: They paste their API keys directly in the cloud window.
100xEngineers: Everything what you're sending here, by the way, especially if you're working with a proprietary model, this data goes to their server.
100xEngineers: Now, yes, there are policies which…
100xEngineers: Anthropic needs to follow, because they are…
100xEngineers: compliant, with, like, all these rules, and HIPAA and GDPR, so they cannot store the information, and they have, like, those rules, but…
100xEngineers: I am always skeptical about, like, what the data I'm sending from my machine, so I don't prefer sending anything which is sensitive information, especially something which is linked to, let's say, my bank account.
100xEngineers: Right now, it is not.
100xEngineers: But if I'm launching this application, let's say in production, where I might need more than 30 requests per minute, I need to put my credit card details to Grok, and that would be sensitive for me, because if I send this information to directly Anthropic, and even, let's say, in middle of that, somebody intercepts that request and find my key, they can get access to my cloud, my account, and then…
100xEngineers: basically, like, misuse it. So, hence, I'll recommend the same approach to all of you. Either you paste your keys manually to your… wherever you're running your application, which becomes cumbersome, but the easiest way, as I told you, is to create a .env file and keep everything there, and
100xEngineers: And then, like, just ask Claude that, hey, use these
100xEngineers: key variables, not the exact key in every… every place. And you can also, like, mark files which clots cannot… clot cannot read. So… so that… that will, like, you will… can make it really, really, safe.
100xEngineers: Right now, it has written a function, so let me, let's see if I have… Something.
100xEngineers: It's written a plan, actually, not the whole function. Now, the reason why it is written the plan is because we have mentioned it to work… work in this manner. So, you can see it created a Claude underscore a clot slash task folder, and in this task folder.
100xEngineers: it has created a plan. This plan tells
100xEngineers: Yeah, this plan tells that always, actually this one.
100xEngineers: that how…
100xEngineers: this diagnose function will work. The goal of this is to implement the diagnose function. It takes the free text input, and this is natural language, something which I'm telling you is a part of spec-driven development. Everything
100xEngineers: even if you are a complete non-coder, or maybe if you have a non-coder manager, like, they can also read and… at least if they understand these concepts, it can make sense to them that, hey, it uses the LLM from GrokCloud, this specific one, using this function which takes the input and then gives the output back. This is the scope. We have a single Python file, one LLM API call, one API key.
100xEngineers: and this Grok. So, the implementation steps, it will… it will exactly tell you what it will do before it implements things.
100xEngineers: It's slightly time-taking process, but one of the
100xEngineers: I would say the most, reliable way of building things with Cloud, because
100xEngineers: before building it, A, you spend a… spend a much less amount of tokens if
100xEngineers: you are reviewing everything before the Clot implements, because sometimes Claude can make assumptions. And this is what I want to, again, focus on here right now, that every single thing, what Claude has written here in the implementation steps, is something which I have not mentioned in the prompt.
100xEngineers: These are the assumptions which Claude has made. So if I would have just asked it, or maybe not used this claud.md file, it would have just implemented all of those things by default.
100xEngineers: And the amount of token it will spend in implementing this is always gonna be much more higher, as compared to just writing about it. So one of the smarter approaches which I do is
100xEngineers: always make sure that I review the implementation plan. Look at the assumptions that Claude is making.
100xEngineers: And… In recent, I would say times.
100xEngineers: since, like, the Model 4.6, the Opus 4.6 and 4.8 came in, I… I started to trust Claude more on these things, although earlier I used to, like, do a very specific review, but because these models are now getting better over time, so the… there's, like, I would say, very, very less cases where I actually, make changes to initial plans, but I still review it so that
100xEngineers: as I said, like, I am the person who is responsible for this application, it's not Claude. If tomorrow Arav generates something which is not useful for him because of this application, he's not gonna blame Claude, he's gonna blame me. So that's basically my responsibility to make sure that I understand everything. So I go through the implementation steps.
100xEngineers: And now this is where you need to… you need to connect the dots from the lectures that we have taken. So, how we actually gonna implement those things? Like, what is the function? What is those, API requests you need to make, and…
100xEngineers: If you have already done that, this is a pretty straightforward plan, by the way, like, which is not doing anything fancy, and it's also mentioning that assumption of what is out of the scope, which is a web UI, which is… I'm correctly identified, so I don't need to build a UI right now. The only thing which I need is just the function, and right out of the function, I want to then maybe expose this function as an API, which also I have not mentioned yet.
100xEngineers: But, So this is… this is… this is great. Now, the second thing which I'll do is…
100xEngineers: now I have clarity on the plan, and I'll ask it to, yes,
100xEngineers: Now, I also know that it's very tempting to just skip this step, and sometimes, especially when you're doing a hackathon or doing something which is, maybe time-sensitive.
100xEngineers: you'll always fall back to just writing the instructions. One of the examples which I can give from my experience here is that
100xEngineers: The amount of…
100xEngineers: Tokens and amount of effort it takes to read a code is always gonna be much more higher as compared to reading a plan.
100xEngineers: One of the incidents for this was, last year I was building one internal
100xEngineers: metric tool, so this is to understand, like, how our cohort metrics were moving, like, how the attendance was, and how, like, the basic operations, what our team used to run. And, I was just, like.
100xEngineers: kind of, like, I would say, busy, and I ended up, like, not following the same approach which I teach most of people. And I realized that everything was almost perfect until the last step.
100xEngineers: Where Claude made one wrong assumption. The wrong assumption was actually to use AWS, which is actually the much bigger wrong assumption, as compared to my own render cloud. So I had, like, my Render subscription already, which I was paying for, and
100xEngineers: And the problem for that was that
100xEngineers: because Claude made that assumption that, hey, everything went well, and now we're gonna, like, deploy it, and I didn't actually review the plan that where Claude is gonna deploy the entire code. And… because by default, AWS is the most popular choice for Cloud deployment option.
100xEngineers: It went ahead and did that.
100xEngineers: And I started doing these back in the day as a long-running task.
100xEngineers: So I went to sleep. I thought I'll just, like, give it a task to Claude that, hey, it already has a code which we tested on local machine, so nothing can go wrong. The only thing right now is just deploying it, which is following the XYZ steps, and I knew in my head that if it will do all of these things, it can just, like, continue, with a deployment on render. But just because I've missed
100xEngineers: that implementation review, and I went ahead and just gave a command, and I went to sleep.
100xEngineers: it took almost, I think 5 to 6 hours, and it did a work of, like, what maybe a potential DevOps engineer would do, and it, like, went ahead, written a code for, like, spinning up
100xEngineers: AWS instances, although thankfully, I didn't have connected any AWS, like.
100xEngineers: account access to the cloud, but it just, like, wasted all the tokens, and the entire codeboard it wrote for me was, like, completely useless. And then I had… when I woke up the next morning, then I realized that everything is, like, kind of just waste for me, and I had to, like, redo all of those things.
100xEngineers: In my case, it's not very, I would say, catastrophic, but I have seen cases where it goes into those side where, let's say if… in my case also, if I had connected my AWS billing account.
100xEngineers: it might have basically, I would say, started all those instances and maybe built the 10x more than what I otherwise could have paid for this. So, that's why, like, these things might sound…
100xEngineers: like, a friction point today, but it's a practice which I want to just, like, share with you, that over time, the more serious projects you will work and build, it just, like, becomes better to, like, have these practices. Okay, so, like, the diagnose function is implemented. Now, let's take a look at the diagnose function, and we can see that
100xEngineers: It's interesting, because…
100xEngineers: now Claude is working on the files that we have started building, and we started doing it. So, it understood the assignment really well, user model.
100xEngineers: And, use the Grok.
100xEngineers: SDK, using the same API key which I have mentioned. So, everything is correct. It came up with a system prompt, which I really like about it, because
100xEngineers: Who is the better person to tell me the prompt?
100xEngineers: what is gonna work for the LM, and I don't think, like, there's anyone better than LM themselves. So I use LMs a lot to help me write prompts.
100xEngineers: Although, like, I need to be clear about what the prompt needs to do. It wrote this entire thing, you are an automation consultant for non-technical business analyst, because I've mentioned that specific detail, and I hope now you see the reason why that specific input was helpful.
100xEngineers: So it gave all the context to the… to the prompt, and then it also mentioned the workflow summary, the pain point, automation suggested tools, and everything.
100xEngineers: I'm okay with that. We can make it better over time, but I think for the MVP, I'll just stick with what it's written. And this is the diagnose function which we started. So the main change Claude did is from 9052 to line number 63. And, so it…
100xEngineers: It does, like… Make a call to…
100xEngineers: this client, and which is our Grok client already, which we've initialized, and it using the model, and it's sending the messages. Now, I can definitely keep a default temperature as well. I'll teach you guys about temperature when we learn the intro to LM, what is this, and what are these values. But for now, if I don't want it, I can actually
100xEngineers: Just keep the model.
100xEngineers: And, the messages, because these are two things which…
100xEngineers: is gonna be relevant for me, and I can understand and review those parts. This is a system prompt, and the reason why it is under role system, because there are two types of roles, actually three types of roles, system, user, and assistant. So you're gonna do these.
100xEngineers: And for the user part, we're gonna add the workflow description, which is coming as the input. That's how we initially started this whole function. Now this function input goes to this chat completion
100xEngineers: a request to GropModel llama 8.1 billion with this system prompt that we have described, and the input which is coming from the user input to this function. And all of this goes to the…
100xEngineers: the model, that model gives us back the response, and we extract the specific content from this response, which is the answer, and then that is what we're gonna return. So this becomes our exact plan.
100xEngineers: So everything works as of now, and it has also written something here. I can test this entire thing, by the way. So the way how I test all of these is just by running the Python files locally. So, let me see if…
100xEngineers: This actually works.
100xEngineers: So, I'm gonna write python main.py file.
100xEngineers: So it…
100xEngineers: It already gave an example workflow, this is the example workflow, and so let's see if it actually gave us the right output or not.
100xEngineers: So it's using a sample workflow?
100xEngineers: Every morning, I download a CSV sales report from our dashboard, open it in Excel, remove duplicates, calculate total per region, paste the summary into a fresh spreadsheet, and email it to my manager. It takes about an hour each day. So this is the description, and this is the output. So, just like what we decided, the input for RF,
100xEngineers: Was this, and the output supposed to be a workflow plan, which can help it to automate that thing.
100xEngineers: So, it's… it's given that you download a daily CSV report, process in Excel, remove, duplicate. So the pain points, it identified automatically, because it gave a whole structure. And this is why it's beneficial to use a smarter model to write prompts.
100xEngineers: Because a smarter model… if I would have done all of this thing with maybe Llama itself, I don't think I would have gotten
100xEngineers: like, this kind of quality, because I've tested Lama models as compared to Opus. They are pretty basic, to be honest. Like, again, no hate against Llama, it's, like, really good what they have done as a community, but it's a slightly older model. So, the reason why
100xEngineers: I chose Opus to do the prompting is because it's a much smarter model, so it does the planning work really well, right? It made a plan that, instead of me giving a random
100xEngineers: output for that, hey, what you can automate. It gave this whole… blueprint.
100xEngineers: So this is a blueprint. Identify the summary.
100xEngineers: pain point, automation opportunities, recommended first automation, and suggested tools, and step-by-step build plan. This was the blueprint which now Lama is following, which is the slightly dumber model.
100xEngineers: But it's kind of doing the job well.
100xEngineers: And this is how I think about using multiple models, which eventually, the more you guys will do these sessions and the more we build things together, you'll get to know that this is, like, a very similar approach how we build teams, right? When you have a really smart person in your team, obviously a senior engineer or a senior expert, or IC,
100xEngineers: he can do a lot of these things, but his bandwidth is very scarce, and his cost is also very high, so you can't put him on each and every task. So the goal is that
100xEngineers: we use the smarter model, the smarter person in the team to do the strategy, to do the planning, and then give these plans to small models, or maybe junior talent, say, junior people and beginners, so that they can follow the plan as it is. That way, we keep the throughput high of the team, and we also, like, don't exhaust our, the senior talent. So this is a great example of doing that, where these two are working together.
100xEngineers: And now I saw the output, I am okay with it, although I can improve it in future, but this looks fine to me.
100xEngineers: And, this is also the first
100xEngineers: part in our journey where we solved a problem. Before this, we had just hypothesis, what we started with, and we identified from this hypothesis, we need one input, one output, and then I determined that, okay, after doing the input and output, we need to write off
100xEngineers: a simple function in Python, and that will take a process, put this input into LLM, get back the plan, and we'll use a specific model here.
100xEngineers: Lake Lama, and then all things are good.
100xEngineers: Now, half of you can continue with this approach, and you can build it.
100xEngineers: Another half, if you want, you can take a pause and you can start thinking about the ELs, which is…
100xEngineers: what I was studying, and the reason I want…
100xEngineers: only half of you do that, because then other half can compare their outputs. Something which you can only learn
100xEngineers: When you have done this kind of development, which means that
100xEngineers: If today, I look at this output, and I say that, hey, I'm happy with this output.
100xEngineers: But I don't tell you that
100xEngineers: why this output is a good output versus, like, what is the difference between this output versus an output that I would have rejected?
100xEngineers: I, myself, might not be able to break this down and articulate it
100xEngineers: Right now. And this requires a deeper level of thinking, maybe which I can… I can spend some time, separately, that
100xEngineers: what makes this workflow automation plan a good plan? Is it…
100xEngineers: the amount of tools it has used, is it amount of hours it has saved? Is it the selection of the workflow? Is it the process of the workflow? Now I can start thinking about the parameters. In a very similar manner, just like if you remember, I was telling you, we had this
100xEngineers: Ogilvi prompt. Mr. Ogil, we have thought about this exactly from the copywriting principle, that what makes this copy good? Is it positioning? Is it unique benefit? Is it headline? Is it tone? Is it emotion, the story, or the call to action, or 15 other things? In the same way.
100xEngineers: before you do any other step, I want you to think about this, that what makes this output good and bad?
100xEngineers: you can… you can take your time about this, although I'll… I'll be trying to, like, finish it up faster, because I need to, like, finish the whole… whole app in the next, like, 40 minutes.
100xEngineers: But I hope you got the point. So this was a… this was a good… good starting point where we have actually, like, finished our core business logic and core business function. Now, everything beyond this point, like, assuming that you have also done your research about what makes this output good, and then you write the evaluation which looks like
100xEngineers: this, and maybe you can add this another prompt, in front of the alert, that every time you generate a plan, which I do a lot of the times, but every time you generate a plan, you can go through this, this whole scoring criteria, and then, like, mark its success or not. Actually, let me do it right now with Claude, and let's see if…
100xEngineers: Claude can help me do that, because…
100xEngineers: I am running short on time, so I'll say… write the… EL prompt.
100xEngineers: Or…
100xEngineers: Now, what I just noticed.
100xEngineers: write the eval for what good output looks like for diagnosis function, and take reference from my Ogilvi prompt. In your case, I would want you to, maybe you can add both the Ogilvi prompt, as well as your own understanding of
100xEngineers: What good output looks like.
100xEngineers: articulated in the golden output pair, because that will really help Claude or any other model which you're using to understand what is the difference between good and bad output pair, and technically what makes it good or what makes it better.
100xEngineers: again, like, it will give you its own assumption, and your job is to review it, and actually see whether it's a good. So, return the eval.prompt.
100xEngineers: And it said that, do you want me to wire this into, main.puff file? I would say, like, yes. And let me see if it has, so this is the eval prompt.md, which is another…
100xEngineers: file it has created, only for the prompt, and this is the whole prompt. Your automation starter is trained to evaluate workflow diagnosis plan for the non-technical business analyst, taking their first step into automation. This is the task, and this is the 15 scoring criteria. It took the inspiration from the same Ogilvy prompt, and
100xEngineers: Just to make it slightly easier to read, I'll…
100xEngineers: Put it in to review this. So it has workflow understanding, pain point, identification, automation, prioritization, beginner feasibility, tool appropriateness, actionability, step sequence, scope, clarity, quick win. A lot of these things are not actually necessary, but
100xEngineers: I'm pretty happy with, like, the kind of, like, first draft it has created. Now I can go and I can make edits to it, I can make changes, and I can also add my own domain knowledge, and this is where
100xEngineers: what I keep saying, the domain knowledge is actually more important when you build an AI system, is because
100xEngineers: This is where you apply that knowledge, which any other AI cannot do. Because everyone can write a prompt, everyone can generate something like this, but only a domain expert can tell whether it is a good quality of eval system or not.
100xEngineers: And that would… that is the one thing which makes the difference among 10 different AI apps which is out there in market. It's not the underlying model, it's not the underlying code which you're writing, it's the way how you are evaluating the output and how you're codifying that judgment.
100xEngineers: So, because I said…
100xEngineers: to add the evaluation, so it has added this eval instruction. Now, what it will do is
100xEngineers: It will evaluate a diagnosis plan against the 15 principles which are stored in this eval prompt rubric.
100xEngineers: And now, every time we generate this workflow, it can, let me also do that.
100xEngineers: Right, no.
100xEngineers: So it has given me the whole evaluation, it has given me the summary, and
100xEngineers: you know, this is one of the output, and if I compare this with the output which I got previously, it's slightly different. I mean, I can't map, like, 1H21 right now, but
100xEngineers: I'm sure, like, the things what it has used right now is gonna be slightly much more deeper, because it has went through this whole, evaluation pipeline, which…
100xEngineers: After generating the diagnosis, it went through the evaluation pipeline, and then it has,
100xEngineers: Actually, I'll ask you to print that as well, because for some reason, it didn't print that evaluation.
100xEngineers: It's storing everything in the, in these variables, as you can see, the plan, the report, the scores, which is slightly overkill for now, but I just want to see everything on my terminal.
100xEngineers: So, I think it's done. Let me just ask it.
100xEngineers: To do it one more time…
100xEngineers: Oh, okay, so what it has done is, because it has taken the inspiration from my Google V prompt, so it's giving me the top 3 areas to improve after this, and it's telling me that, hey, these are things which you can do, start with the Power Query, and you'll be amazed at how quickly automation can transform in the practice things.
100xEngineers: Now you can see that the workflow which I got from previous, every time I'm doing it, it's actually generating slightly much more deeper and denser workflow. Now, not every time it is actually making sense, which means that maybe, like, sometimes it's just, like, adding things because
100xEngineers: of the eval, and that is where you need to use your judgment at whether the actual output is getting better or not. And I think that's the whole cycle which… which can keep on, say, running, I would say.
100xEngineers: multiple times, so you can, like, do this part. The first time when I designed my eval for something like this, I think I ran it, like, at least, like, 15-20 times to understand whether this eval system is working or not.
100xEngineers: And and then over time, I got some intuition that, hey, this was a part where it was missing, and then added or removed a few more criterias. That's the same process which I would…
100xEngineers: I would also recommend you to do. I'll basically, like, take a…
100xEngineers: next gear here, because we have spent a lot of time into building the core function, which I actually don't mind, because this is the core of everything what we have done. Like, literally, I can just…
100xEngineers: take this function, what we have built, and I can walk into Arav's room, or maybe get on a call with Arav, and I can just take the input instruction, which I can just paste it here.
100xEngineers: Which is my sample workflow. I'll replace this and I'll paste exactly what Arav is gonna say on call, and I can manually generate the plan, I can send this plan to Arav. Although this… taking the input and sending the output is manual, but the entire process is automated. And this is something which I would recommend all of you to do. Whenever you're building your first app, don't go beyond this part.
100xEngineers: And, like, start building everything else. And that's a common mistake which people do
100xEngineers: And that's where the most amount of time they actually lose. This is a quick learning from doing a lot of hackathons and conducting hackathons, that
100xEngineers: Or maybe any kind of short… Time-sensitive sprint.
100xEngineers: If your job is to just solve the problem, not to build the best solution or good-looking solution, or I would say, like, building the most sophisticated, fancy solution which can cater to, let's say, hundreds or millions of people, but your job is to, like, solve the problem first.
100xEngineers: if you go with this approach, you'll be able to move much more faster, because AI, I'm not…
100xEngineers: thinking about what is the best UI I can choose for it, what is the best database I can choose for it, what is the best deployment platform I can choose. And my entire last, like, almost, I would say, like, I spent, like, a good amount of time here, it's more than what I expected, but as I said, like, I don't trigger that because this is something which I'll always recommend as well. This is a core business logic of it. And once this is done.
100xEngineers: I can just take this and start, like, producing more output, and everything beyond that is where I don't mind even if Claude takes over and starts writing everything, because I know that what I want to do once my diagnosis function is up and running.
100xEngineers: And the major important part here is that it is actually solving the problem which I observed.
100xEngineers: And I wrote down as the hypothesis, which was my bet, and I generated the output, I did it multiple times, and I wrote the evals of what good looks like, encoded it, and then I tested it out. So, even though it doesn't look good, but it solves a problem. Now, beyond this, the goal is
100xEngineers: just take this function and expose it to the world. And this expose is basically what we do when we learned about the APIs, especially the fast APIs as a package in Python, which helps you to, like, take this function and expose it to the world. Because once you know this function is working for you manually, then you can tell the world that, hey, I have built something which is valuable, and now you guys can use it, and maybe you can charge for this as well. And that's basically, like,
100xEngineers: a cleaner way to, like, evolve from an MVP function to then maybe an MVP API, and then UI. So, you see the difference between this MVP workflow, which I'm building, is
100xEngineers: more business code logic first, and then coming to the UI at the end, versus how we learned everything was starting from the UI and then going back. So this is also a change which I want to do, because we have already crossed those parts, and now you understand all those things, so always
100xEngineers: Take this approach, if you want to save time and maybe focus on problem solving more than the other parts of it.
100xEngineers: Now, as I said, like, the second thing which I'll do is I need to understand that, oh, hey, what kind of APIs I need. With Python, we have, like, one of the best API choices.
100xEngineers: which I personally like is FastAPI, Clean Framework, although Python gives us more frameworks than FastAPI itself, but I… I keep that as a technology stack, because it's lean, it's better, and it just, like, works for me. So what I'll do is, as now I'm happy with the input-output, I have the evals working for me.
100xEngineers: I'll go back to the cloud, and I'll say, okay, convert…
100xEngineers: create… a fast API endpoint.
100xEngineers: for… Exposing my diagnose function.
100xEngineers: Now, here you can actually give more specific input. I… I'll actually first look at the plan, what Claude creates, and then give my inputs, but…
100xEngineers: If you already know that maybe you can give the specific method that you want to use, the get method, POST method, maybe in the chat you can tell me, like, what could be the method that you would choose if you have to build an API like that, if you're doing a diagnose API which takes the input and generates the plan. What do you think, what could be the method?
100xEngineers: No, Shefali, I said that I pasted it from the GitHub. This is the exact one which I shared.
100xEngineers: So this is a cloud instruction.
100xEngineers: I'll actually paste it here as well, for somebody who is following along.
100xEngineers: Yes, but I think all of you are right, we will be using POST as an endpoint, because it's generating something as a plan. Now I have the plan ready with me, and
100xEngineers: So this is a plan. The endpoint is telling me that what all things it'll post, or it'll create. Diagnose is something which I want. It takes the workflow descriptions, generates the output.
100xEngineers: And I can do it, like, from anywhere in the world. It also has added the evaluate endpoint, which is interesting, because I didn't ask for it. I just asked for, like, one endpoint, but it said, hey, we can add evaluate, which means that
100xEngineers: the functionality that we built within the code, which was initially supposed to just evaluate the plan that LM generates as part of this function, now Claude is suggesting that we can actually take it out, and we can create a separate function, which is just doing
100xEngineers: maybe evals could become its own function, which is actually a very good strategy, and something which you can learn is what I call the decomposition.
100xEngineers: if you are building a function, which is… you start with a core business logic with one single thing, but over time, this function becomes bigger. You add more eval, and eval has now, like, a whole one-page prompt, and then there might be a different model which you're using to evaluate the output.
100xEngineers: Because you need, like, a smarter model. This is also known as LLM as a judge.
100xEngineers: pattern, where you use another LLM to judge the output of a different LLM. So you can do all of those things, and what we do is we just break it down into different functions. So we just create one more function, that is the eval, and we write
100xEngineers: all the input of this eval, which could be the description coming from this, or could be the plan coming from it. In this case, now, the moment we
100xEngineers: Take this function out.
100xEngineers: this function also becomes a candidate for an API, which means the same thing what Klaus is suggesting right now, that then anyone can also use your eval function, just like how I'm sharing my
100xEngineers: OgleBee Copy Reviewer with everybody, you can create emails and you can start sharing these evils for your industry, right? And maybe, like, that can become one of the offerings. So, which also means that
100xEngineers: you don't need to always depend on your own server to generate the plan. Maybe the user can come with a plan. So tomorrow, if Arav, in our case, the way how I'd look at this change, if Arav already knows a workflow.
100xEngineers: But it needs help. Arab needs help to understand whether this is a good plan or a bad plan.
100xEngineers: RF can just paste the plan, and instead of doing the diagnose API, we can just make a call to eval API.
100xEngineers: And that way, we start making our backend more…
100xEngineers: modular, as well as, like, more, adaptable. And this is, like, also a thought process, like.
100xEngineers: how you build something from, like, a core function, and a core logic, and then expand it over time, rather than you doing everything together and thinking about 10 different things, and then, like, trying to, like, make sense of it. Okay, let me come back, because I think I spent good time here.
100xEngineers: So…
100xEngineers: And it may also ask it to… meanwhile, I'm doing it, you can implement these APIs, because I'm… I'm pretty much… I'm fine with it, I'll say.
100xEngineers: One more thing which I will write here is after implementing the APIs, is because I'm using this model approach, so I want to
100xEngineers: do the testing. So, one of the…
100xEngineers: One of the best things about APIs and functions, and this whole programming approach.
100xEngineers: This is, by the way, called functional programming, which is one of the oldest paradigm of writing programs. There are multiple other ways of doing this.
100xEngineers: again, very open-ended, very biased, but I think, in my opinion, this is something which I have… which got an… or which gave me more clarity, and I got more output from this way of thinking, breaking every single thing down into functions, input-output, and then decomposing it into multiple other functions, and then I can reuse those parts, like, over time.
100xEngineers: So… This is what, like, Recall as, functional programming.
100xEngineers: Now, because we have functions, we have APIs, we have input and output, we also know what is a good quality output looks like.
100xEngineers: Because that's assuming what we have done, that we can write tests for it.
100xEngineers: Remember the golden input-output pair, which I initially mentioned? You can use those golden input-output pair as well. Right now, I don't have it with me, but if you are solving a problem statement, I would highly recommend you to add those golden input-output pair, and ask Claude, or whatever model you're using, to use these golden input-output pairs
100xEngineers: To then write the test cases.
100xEngineers: So that it understands what is the good output looks like, and then always try to compare it with it. So that way, like, if tomorrow you change the model and the model starts performing poorly, you can catch those bugs, and your
100xEngineers: Python function or Python program where the tests are written can flag all of those things.
100xEngineers: So it said it has implemented the APIs, and it has wrote… written the 101… sorry, 111 lines of test code, by the way. So these are tests.
100xEngineers: test health, okay, which means that if everything is up and fine, that's the basic test. If the backend server is throwing to 200,
100xEngineers: Test diagnose success, which means the happy path returns plan. Test diagnose empty string, which means that the minimum length of the plan
100xEngineers: needs to be at least one. Diagnosis should not be empty. Diagnosis missing field, diagnosis value error. So now you can start thinking that just by writing one simple command, Claude actually… actually, Claude is very smart in terms of writing tests, and that's something which I also use it a lot.
100xEngineers: Whereby I just dedicate most of my judgment about writing tests, because I know that this is something which it can do even better than me.
100xEngineers: So it has written, like, quite an extensive test case scenarios, and I can just always come back and verify that,
100xEngineers: What's the… This is the test API, so it's…
100xEngineers: taking the sample workflow and this plan, and as I said, like, right now it's using the fake plan, but in future, like, you can add your golden product repairs, and these are the test functions that it's using. So now, every time you make changes, you have a deterministic system. Now, this is where I would like to also
100xEngineers: Circle back on this part.
100xEngineers: We discussed about building the AI system, which is a combination of deterministic system and probabilistic systems. So right now, what we are doing is we are using the Lama 8.1 billion parameter model to generate the output plan, which otherwise we could not have generated from any other
100xEngineers: Python application, the same quality of plan, but we use that
100xEngineers: probabilistic model to generate that quality output, but this gives us another problem which I mentioned, double-edged sword, that you cannot verify it very easily. So we wrote a whole eval prompt for it, where we use another prompt to judge their output, and then we added
100xEngineers: But test cases, which is a deterministic part of the system that is using the golden input-output pair, which test
100xEngineers: that… what is that one input and what is the one output that it should give, and this part lives in the deterministic side. So what we are trying to do is, we are mixing both of these systems, and we're using the best capabilities of both of them. I know probabilistic systems can
100xEngineers: do things more flexibly, but cannot generate reliable output, and I know deterministic thing… deterministic systems can build more reliable stuff, but they don't have that creative freedom. So, this is also, like, a good intersection point to think about it, like, where we are writing
100xEngineers: the test cases, and we are also writing the eval. So this… this is what covering the…
100xEngineers: the, the, I would say, evaluation for the deterministic, the non-deterministic part, the probabilistic one, and the test one is covering the test cases for the deterministic section.
100xEngineers: So okay, now we have the API and the test up and running. Now I can see that this is also the fast API, which is already there. And at this point, I have, like, a bunch of things here. So what I'll do is I'll now ask it to first
100xEngineers: Push everything to… My, server.
100xEngineers: So that I… I can start, like, at least testing things. Although I can run it locally as well, I can ask it running locally, but I… I want to just, like, quickly…
100xEngineers: push it to the server so that I can start deploying it. And this is also where I'll take another choice or decision, is that where will we deploy our API? So we have multiple options. One is, as I said, like, could be the traditional hyperscaler clouds, which means AWS, GCP, Azure. Right now, I don't want to take the headache of, like.
100xEngineers: finding and spinning up a new server there, and, like, doing the configuration.
100xEngineers: So what I'll do is I'll try to find the most minimal, viable product for that, which is what I initially recommended as well. This is the platform called…
100xEngineers: render.
100xEngineers: So, render is… just think about render as of…
100xEngineers: What are the wrapper around these cloud platforms? And what it does, it gives you, like, a very easy to get started
100xEngineers: method to start deploying your APIs, what you have. There are multiple ways to deploy things. I'll cover this maybe in a specific
100xEngineers: section, which I maybe write as a good… I'm writing, like, a whole guidebook for all of you guys. Like, how do you take decisions about all of these things? I think I've written one which I sent to all of you. I'm sure, like, some of you would have
100xEngineers: I would say, like, Reddit. If not, then I would recommend you, when you're doing your hackathon, you can maybe, like, take a look at that. That was about databases. But the other one…
100xEngineers: which I'm writing is about the choosing the cloud platforms, or the choosing deployment platforms. So this… this is one of the, core decisions which actually
100xEngineers: affects the overall cost and also the reliability. I could choose something like Versal, I can choose something like, maybe other, like, even Hugging Face Spaces, but there's a very specific reason which… the reason why I'm using it is because
100xEngineers: it gives me that one instance that I can control completely. As compared to
100xEngineers: let's say, if I go with a…
100xEngineers: AWS Lambda function, which is a type of another deployment service, or maybe versatile functions, cloud functions, or serverless functions.
100xEngineers: they don't give me access to the whole machine. They just take my code and run that code as a function to different machines, and that is what it's known as serverless functions, or cloud functions, as a concept. So, in this particular case, I do want to control the machine.
100xEngineers: For a few reasons. One is that right now, I don't know that how many people will be using my app.
100xEngineers: I might need to spend more time to request, to actually calculate the request, because I'm using LLM. LLMs can take time sometimes, because if the… I'm using the thinking model tomorrow to replace, the LAM model, it can take up to, let's say, 1 or 2 minutes.
100xEngineers: And the problem with most of the cloud functions right now is that they have a timeout problem, which means that if you're using something like AWS Lambda or Virtual Cloud Functions, which is another alternative to Render, by the way, the reason I'm telling you is because you at least are aware of that, why I'm choosing this platform, is because these guys have timeout
100xEngineers: problems. So, you can't run, like.
100xEngineers: API calls which are going beyond a certain threshold, and I don't want that kind of restriction, especially if I'm running multiple LLM calls. So that's one other reason why I'm choosing it, and another one is it's completely free of cost for my hobby projects. So these are two major reasons why I'm using this platform. Now, one thing which I'll do is I'll create a new project here, and I'll try to connect this project with my GitHub repository.
100xEngineers: So, I'll go back to my GitHub, which I created.
100xEngineers: But in order for me to connect and deploy it, first I need to push it to the GitHub. So, two-step process, whatever we have done, we'll push it to GitHub, and then we'll connect this GitHub repository to render. That is the deployment part, where we have our backend model up and running. So, I'll go back quickly, and we'll start the deployment process.
100xEngineers: So it automatically did something smart, that it added gitignal file, something which I would recommend all of you to do.
100xEngineers: Which means that there are files always which you don't want your…
100xEngineers: public platforms to know. I don't… when I'm sharing this file with Render, when I'm sharing this file with GitHub specifically, I am right now running a public repository.
100xEngineers: So, if I don't put .env in my gitignore file, it will just expose this entire file to the internet, and anyone can use it on my profile, on github.com.
100xEngineers: which will, again, expose my API keys. So, the smarter strategy and the safer strategy here is to put everything in .gitignore file, and the way you do it, you just, like, create this .gitignore file, and then write the names of the files which you don't want to get, I would say, pushed into the GitHub repository.
100xEngineers: So it's… it has done all of these things, and it has said that, your Grok API was sitting in a plain text file, it was not pushed.
100xEngineers: But you have shared it in this session, I recommend notating the keys, which I agree, I actually would have not used that file right now, and I would have excluded it from the cloud, but completely fine as of now, because I am… I'm about to, like, just change the API key after this anyways.
100xEngineers: Let me just confirm whether everything is pushed to GitHub or not. So, we just…
100xEngineers: Push things, this is the repository, and this is the…
100xEngineers: I can see all the changes here. It's reflected. This is the main.py file, and actually, this is the exact same code which we are running on our local machine. It has the Grok API key as a variable, but I can see there is not any .env file. There is one example file, which is only saying that this is the example, and this is how anyone can clone it. So, that's how we…
100xEngineers: The database guide was shared on the LMS forum. I'll just check with my team if it was available for both code and no code. If not, then I'll just, like, ask them to share with everybody, but I posted it on the LMS.
100xEngineers: now I have everything on my main branch. So this is also another part which is very important when you work, especially on the deployment part, is
100xEngineers: I recommend you to, like, create multiple branches.
100xEngineers: for the development work. So, for example, let's say you are working on a project which is now getting used by an external user. Let's say I want to start using my app, and then I have to make a change. I don't want to
100xEngineers: push a change while RF is generating a plan, because maybe…
100xEngineers: if something goes wrong, let's say if my API started throwing an error because of some small mistake, Arro's workflow will be messed up because of the change which I pushed at that time. So what I'll usually recommend doing is that create one more branch, so you can create multiple branches, both from CLI, from
100xEngineers: UI as well, so the easiest way, you can just create a new branch. You can ask it to just, let's say, create a dev branch, and this is a source branch, which means it's going to be a copy of the source branch, that means
100xEngineers: whatever code is written as of now, which is present on this repository, I'll keep a copy of that code, and I'll create a new branch from it. Now, the reason why this is better is because now I can use DevB branch for pushing all my changes and testing everything. And once I'm
100xEngineers: happy with all the changes, then I will merge these changes to the main branch. So that way, I'll just, like, have always one development environment ready with me, so even if
100xEngineers: let's say Arab is using the main app, and I push the change relative dev, and dev started breaking, Arav's work won't get affected. And only when I will fix this change, which is now I have tested after deploying it and everything is fixed.
100xEngineers: So this is where most people do the QA. So QA work starts here, which is quality assurance, and where people do automated testing. One other tool which I can recommend, I already have it on my GitHub command line. This is called Code Rabbit.
100xEngineers: works well, especially for beginners, because you want your code to be reviewed. It's also free for public…
100xEngineers: projects, so if you are building any public project right now, maybe as part of the next hackathon, which you'll be building, or just, like, in general, what you are building, it's gonna be free for all of you, so you don't need to, again, pay anything for this, and it's a good way to also do a
100xEngineers: review of whatever you are pushing, so something which is, like, worth noting down. I'll come back to this part, and although, like, right now, I'm… as I said, like, for this session, I'll try to just keep everything on the main.
100xEngineers: And I'll now go back to the render, and I'll create a new project.
100xEngineers: Yeah, I might need to pause this one, so I'll pause the older MCP project, MVP1.
100xEngineers: I'll do this a spring…
100xEngineers: The reason why I'm deleting the project is because Render allows, free projects, I think up to only one. So I'll create a one… actually, two free projects.
100xEngineers: I'll create this C7 workflow diagnosis.
100xEngineers: and rotate the production environment only. Now, this is where it's helpful. So, I create a new service.
100xEngineers: When I create a… click on this new service, this is the option which I'll choose. It's called Web Services. This is helpful for building your backend API servers.
100xEngineers: So we'll click on New Web Service, and because I have logged in, so one thing which I missed is that when you are creating the account on Render, make sure you log in with your GitHub account, it becomes easier for you to connect your GitHub repository. So because I logged in and signed up on this platform called Render from my GitHub, it can access my GitHub repository, which are publicly available.
100xEngineers: So this is the one which I'm already working, and I've pushed all my code here, so it can automatically fetch…
100xEngineers: that, hey, this is the language you're using, this is the branch, and then the region. I'm using the free one, so I'll go with the Singapore Southeast Asia. If you are in US, you can go with the US West, or whatever's the nearest location for you.
100xEngineers: In the free plan. This is the build command, pip install requirements, and now something which I need to mention here is a start command. So, because usually Python apps can run by writing the Python space
100xEngineers: app.py file. In this case, the app which we want to run is,
100xEngineers: is in a fast API. So the Fast API works specifically when you want to
100xEngineers: like, using the Yubicon command. So, in this Yubicon command.
100xEngineers: Let me actually just write down this… particular command.
100xEngineers: Yeah, so this is the command which I'm gonna paste here. Yubicon main colon app, and the reason why I'm doing main.app is because whatever is the name of your file.
100xEngineers: So if I go back here, the file which we have created where our core logic works is this file.
100xEngineers: So I'll write the main file, you don't need to write the .py, because it assumes that everything is gonna be written in Python.
100xEngineers: So, this mentions the name of the file.
100xEngineers: This app means that it has the FastAPI app server, and then it'll host it on… port 000.
100xEngineers: And this is a dynamic port, which means that whatever port is available, at that moment, it will use that, instead of you giving a local number. So, this is, like, one command which you need to write if you are deploying any Fast API on Render. That's the only change. Everything else, I'll keep it
100xEngineers: like, for free. Right now, like, I'll do this.
100xEngineers: And this is where I can add the variables. So, the Grok…
100xEngineers: variable which I added, the Glock API key, because now I'm doing it, this is my, secrets, like, all the things which are, like, API key, I'll mention here. So that…
100xEngineers: nobody else can see that. And this is also another thing which I was mentioning, that because we are deploying it on render.
100xEngineers: So it's, better for me to, like.
100xEngineers: store the information there, as compared to if we build everything on Hugging Face Spaces, because Spaces' account is generally publicly available, even the code base of that.
100xEngineers: So it's… it's a bit better to, like, do it here.
100xEngineers: Let me just do this…
100xEngineers: Okay, so I have added the API key, and now let me deploy the web service.
100xEngineers: So this is the whole deployment happening right now. It will show you all the logs. If anything goes wrong while you're deploying something, it will showcase everything here.
100xEngineers: By looking at the time, I think I might need to extend…
100xEngineers: things to the… another 15-20 more minutes, so… but I'll try to build everything before I, like, wrap it up. Actually, we are… we're almost there, because the major part of our workflow was, what building the whole backend and the core logic is there. Now, as I said, like, everything I can fast-track with Claude, because I understand
100xEngineers: beyond this point, what I need is… Just this system.
100xEngineers: We just deployed our backend.
100xEngineers: to render, and we have LLM, which is coming from the Grok.
100xEngineers: And, we also have created the fast APIs, which means anyone can talk to it, whether it's, like, our front-end.
100xEngineers: And we learned Gradio UI from our UI lecture, so we can just, like, quickly spin up one UI from the Gradio, and meanwhile, render is happening, what I'll do is, I'll actually, like, do that, and
100xEngineers: I'll… I'll maybe, like, add the… the new UI file here, so let me just… Open, hugging Face spaces.
100xEngineers: This is the Hugging Face…
100xEngineers: This is where I'll be keeping my front end, so I'll go to plus new space, and I'll say C7 workflow.
100xEngineers: Diagnosis… And, I'll keep the graduio as it is.
100xEngineers: public, and I'll create the space.
100xEngineers: I'll create one file so that…
100xEngineers: everything is gonna be there. And I have already done that, by the way, so I think… actually, let me just…
100xEngineers: Get this file code.
100xEngineers: This was the old code which I have written.
100xEngineers: About my simple chat interface, if you remember.
100xEngineers: Which we built.
100xEngineers: So, it accesses everything into, your… from the backend URL, which basically gives us access to the Diagnos API directly.
100xEngineers: And we know that we have just built a diagnose API, which we have also tested. So what the Gradio Chat interface is right now doing, it's,
100xEngineers: taking the workflow description, sending it back as the JSON to this backend URL. If it doesn't find backend URL, it falls back to the local host. In this case, we will store everything in the backend URL. And this is why… and this is how I will connect the backend and the front-end. So first, I'll…
100xEngineers: push all of these changes. I'll directly commit it to a…
100xEngineers: file. And then I'll go to the Settings tab.
100xEngineers: in the variables.
100xEngineers: I'll keep the name backend URL, and here I need to put the backend URL, which needs to be live, so that Hugging Face Spaces, which lives in a different machine, can talk to it. So, what I'll do is, quickly, I'll…
100xEngineers: Go back to… My… Render.
100xEngineers: Okay, there's something which has failed, so let me see what happened.
100xEngineers: Oh, we don't have the requirements filed, so this is something which…
100xEngineers: is a common error. Now, the problem is, Something which I can explain.
100xEngineers: If I open my cursor right now.
100xEngineers: we have installed a bunch of things. Like, we have FastAPI, we have Pydantic, we have, also test suits, but there is no way for us to tell render, as I told you, right? Like, render is a machine, which is not our machine. We ran, or we asked Claude to run pip install command, which installed everything.
100xEngineers: But Render doesn't know, so the first thing which I found out, and this is a mistake which is done by Claude, so we can all point out to Claude right now. I can push my blame to it, and I say.
100xEngineers: Hey, you missed… Adding the requirements file.
100xEngineers: Deployment failed, so…
100xEngineers: Do the test, and
100xEngineers: Yes, we can do pip freeze, requirements as well. Thanks, Ansh, for the command. If you want to do it manually.
100xEngineers: Now, the reason why I asked Claude is so that it can also find anything else which can potentially block her deployment.
100xEngineers: But yeah, that's a… actually command what Hunch has mentioned, just to…
100xEngineers: put it on my screen. This is the command which you can write as well. Pip freeze r…
100xEngineers: lesson symbol and requirements.txt, so it'll create a requirements.txt file.
100xEngineers: In my case, it has already done that, and let me just quickly review it.
100xEngineers: One more thing which, again, it has made us small adjustment.
100xEngineers: Which is, again, slightly…
100xEngineers: opinionated. I would like to start the project without putting the version numbers here. Now, if you are somebody who is
100xEngineers: good at remembering things and good at, like, keeping track of different versions, you can go ahead and lock these versions. That's a good practice in production, by the way, so that if a new version of, let's say, Python or FastAPI comes in, which has a breaking change, that does not break everything in your production system.
100xEngineers: But when you're building it out, especially, like, unless, until you have tested it completely to a couple of users, and you're happy with the versions, because maybe I realized that while I'm doing this, FastAPI launched a new version which has an update or a fix or something which I need, and then I keep updating those things. I need to always come back to this and do that. So there are two options right now. If you are happy with this.
100xEngineers: And this is all… how should you make a decision, is if you're happy with all the…
100xEngineers: code that is there, which is running on your machine, helping RF and helping multiple people, and everything is working flawlessly, smooth and fine, then you can come back and you can lock the versions. This is a good way to, like, look at this requirements or TXC. But if you have not done that.
100xEngineers: In the initial run, you can just keep these fields empty. And you can just, like, always rely on the latest update.
100xEngineers: Until you found that, hey, everything is working well.
100xEngineers: And once you have that clarity, after that, you can post it. In my case, because I think, as of now, I am okay locking these versions.
100xEngineers: So I'll just, like, keep it like this, and I will… Also… Push these changes.
100xEngineers: One more hack here, just to, for people who are…
100xEngineers: curious to do all of this thing, man, like, from CLI itself, if you want Claude to take over this whole…
100xEngineers: creation of your render service.
100xEngineers: you can also download the Render MCP. So Render has the MCP server. We'll learn more about what is exactly MCP, but for now, you can think of Render is directly available with tools like Cloud Code from the CLI, which means that it can
100xEngineers: Give access to your account.
100xEngineers: to Cloud Code, and it can, like, take all the actions, so you don't need to come to this page manually, which is… is also, like, a
100xEngineers: Very useful feature when you're doing multiple deployments and making multiple changes every single day.
100xEngineers: Let me see if we have a push… Which we did.
100xEngineers: Okay, just did that.
100xEngineers: So ideally, it should now restart the deployment process.
100xEngineers: And… let me see if it triggers anything.
100xEngineers: So this is also a way to do manually, like, if for some reason, let's say, it doesn't trigger any change.
100xEngineers: Usually, this… this is something which I discussed, I think, maybe earlier. If you go to the settings tab of Render.
100xEngineers: The… Deploy, commit the auto-deploy.
100xEngineers: If it is sent on on commit, it means that, by default, Render automatically deploys your service whenever you update its current configuration. So, disable to handle deployment manually.
100xEngineers: So right now it's… it's doing…
100xEngineers: on commit, and but if you want to make changes to that, if you don't want to deploy every time you make commit to this branch, then you can, like, change that logic. Let me come back to it and see if we have…
100xEngineers: Meanwhile, this is happening. What I'll do is, I'll…
100xEngineers: I'll use my other service, but…
100xEngineers: So I have, like, one more service switch… He's running.
100xEngineers: So this is the one I'll just, like, use because this is live as of now.
100xEngineers: One other thing which I think Claude is overthinking, and it's added, like, a couple of steps here in the render YAML file.
100xEngineers: So sometimes it can happen. Like, also, one of the reasons why I want to do it live with all of you is because you could see that even the best model, so I'm not using, like, something like Sonnet, I'm using the Opus 4.8 right now at high thinking effort.
100xEngineers: This is one of the frontier models right now, which is making mistakes like this.
100xEngineers: And the only way to actually assess these mistakes is if you know what it is doing. And that's what I constantly, like, remind every single person, like, who is here, is that
100xEngineers: yes, you can vibe code your way out, but you will very soon likely to have a bottleneck like this. Maybe, right now, what is happening with us, it's like… it's time to, like, over-engineering… or over-engineer things.
100xEngineers: Which is not needed right now, so… and because of that, like, our… the backend was, like, failing. And initially, it didn't push the requirements file because
100xEngineers: we didn't mention it, and Claude itself, like, forgot to, like, add it. So this could be another, maybe, like, a part fault of me and part fault of Claude as well. So there are a couple of things, right, which we identified, right? Maybe, like.
100xEngineers: Maybe a bottleneck that you will also face if you start using the same model, or maybe similar models in the same workflow. So maybe next time onwards, you can keep a track.
100xEngineers: One of the things which I really like about a whole of this approach is that
100xEngineers: As we have started the journey with plan and review.
100xEngineers: Each and every step is documented right now.
100xEngineers: how many times, this entire thing happened, and, like, whenever I basically do the task, So, ding.
100xEngineers: So, I'll… I have, like, all the diagnosis function here, but… I think there's… I'll do one…
100xEngineers: one part, which I think it has not added. What I'll do is I… I'll ask Claude.
100xEngineers: That whenever you're making change.
100xEngineers: So, to be honest, at this point, I'm just reminding Claude what I've already done.
100xEngineers: Which is slightly strange behavior, because it hasn't happened yet.
100xEngineers: I think I'm using a fresh account right now for this one, because I exhausted the limit from my older account, so maybe it's, it doesn't have the whole…
100xEngineers: previous history and the training. But usually what I was trying to say is that if it would have, like, I would say remembered the instruction which I gave it, it would have logged each and everything out. And even right now, we have all the logs, but in the commits format.
100xEngineers: But this is something which is not very, I would say,
100xEngineers: Easy to readable in a natural language format.
100xEngineers: So, what I need is, like, exactly what Claude did in each and every commit, in each and every change. It should also log it under the task folder, just like how it first created a plan for us. So, I think right now it only logged the plan, but after that,
100xEngineers: I think because we started, like, building directly with Claude, so it's… it didn't actually, log everything out.
100xEngineers: But this is something which I was… I still recommend. Oh, actually, right now, I got it. So, this is a better way, so, of doing it. Now you can… now you can see that there is a file called render deployfix.
100xEngineers: The reason why I was trying to, like, showcase this is because next time Claude will face this same problem, it has a log of the previous things. And if I would have been using my older account from which I use, like, for my primary development.
100xEngineers: that already has these things in the memory, which means that all the common mistakes that Claude makes every single time, it is there in those logs. So that becomes a very good self-improving loop over time, which it can do. So next time, if I'm using the same Claude model from the same session.
100xEngineers: it will remember that it made a mistake last time because the requirement file was missing, or because, like, this particular thing was missing. So…
100xEngineers: Yeah, just to go back and see.
100xEngineers: If we have… Something working.
100xEngineers: Oh, wow, so our… Finally, the workflow is deployed live.
100xEngineers: Thanks to Claude, I was slightly more harsh to it.
100xEngineers: Now, let me just check if my APIs are working. So, another way how I check in FastAPI is by using the docs tool. This is Workflow Diagnosis API, all of it's documented live on my workflow, and I am happy with it. So, this is the Diagnosed one, which I'll be using.
100xEngineers: So, I'll copy this whole URL. In your case, when you deploy it, you can copy this URL. This is the URL which I was telling you we can paste in our front-end. So, the front-end code which we had here.
100xEngineers: This is a 1, and I can…
100xEngineers: Add a new variable.
100xEngineers: backend underscore URL.
100xEngineers: Okay, one thing I think I missed here is…
100xEngineers: I need to add the diagnose endpoint as well.
100xEngineers: Because it's just using the diagnose right now.
100xEngineers: So, I have this… C7 workflow diagnosis tool on render.com slash diagnose, which is connected to my…
100xEngineers: app.ui file, and it's restarting, and it has now the interface with me, and hopefully it can give me the…
100xEngineers: output, let me see if I can test something right now.
100xEngineers: Okay, it got some kind of plan, the workflow summary, and all of this is coming from the backend, which we just deployed and built live on this whole app. So, in a way, we actually finished
100xEngineers: The whole full-stack development, which is around building the… UI backend API?
100xEngineers: Let me just find this one. Yes.
100xEngineers: So now we have, two major things to choose from. Like, A, the database. I'm not going to repeat the database part, because this is something which I just covered in the last lecture.
100xEngineers: What I would share this as, maybe you can continue with the doc that I shared, and then you can choose the right database from the problem statement. I have used something like Superbase for there.
100xEngineers: What I would…
100xEngineers: like to add as a last point here is, how do we now prepare it for a scale? Let's say now I launch this, I deployed it live, and I now want to share it with Arav, and Arav said, okay, I have more people like me who I want to learn, who I want to share this with.
100xEngineers: But I can't keep a track of who is using how many APIs, because the main bottleneck for me, and this is where I do the napkin math, which I call… so the main bottleneck for me, if you know, remember, everything what we have done here.
100xEngineers: If I go back and, let's say, do it.
100xEngineers: This is…
100xEngineers: the understanding of my current tech stack. Every decision which I've made in the last, 2 hours.
100xEngineers: is because of those things, which I have available for the free tiers. With Grok LLM, I can make 30 requests per minute, which means that 250 times RF can click under 1 minute, or…
100xEngineers: 215 unique users can click, and maybe, like, send messages to my application. But the moment this limit cross, within a minute, it will start throwing the error that you are out of your free tier.
100xEngineers: for Superbase, like, this is the authentication which I'm targeting, and if I add the database as well, all of those are actually gonna be, like, much…
100xEngineers: less of a worry, which means that Superbase, if I use for authentication, which I was, like, the another part I'm coming… coming to,
100xEngineers: it can handle, under the free tier, up to 50,000 plus monthly active users. Like, you can use 50,000…
100xEngineers: people who can use this and authenticate using this thing uniquely. Right now, if I share with all the people, and that's what I was coming up with, the 250 number, let's say all the people of C7 cohort, the max I'm gonna reach is 250, which is, like, 0.5% of the ceiling.
100xEngineers: Same goes for Superbase database. If I use the database to store everything, all the conversations, it's gonna be, like, hardly few MB of conversation, and even if, let's say, people use it, the text-based conversations do not cross, like.
100xEngineers: tens of MBs, even for, like, maybe thousands, or you can say sub-hundred thousands as well. So it's also, like, something which is very minimal for us. Only when I actually cross, like.
100xEngineers: I would select a very heavy load, then I might need to think about this.
100xEngineers: The only bottleneck for me is the Crocket LM API, and that's what I get to know about this, and this is something which I also want you to think about it. Where are the bottlenecks before you start scaling and before you start thinking about the next steps of what you want to do next. Now, because of this, I'll add… I'll make two decisions.
100xEngineers: One, I will cap the limits.
100xEngineers: For… per user.
100xEngineers: let's say Arav is using the app, I want Arav to first get authenticated, because only then I can…
100xEngineers: put it in my database, and I can tell that, hey, this guy has used the unique
100xEngineers: ID and password, it's a new user in my database.
100xEngineers: And, every new user gets not more than, let's say, 10 request… per minute.
100xEngineers: So whenever Arav is making more than 10 requests per minute, I'll basically say that, hey, Arav, can you wait for another minute, because I'm reaching a limit. Now, the other plan for this, definitely I can add my credit card details, and I can just, like, increase these limits, which, again, won't cost me a lot, so I've done the math myself, and you can do that, this math, it's very easy. You just, like, track each and every input and output.
100xEngineers: of your request, and then you can calculate it based on the average of how much input you are sending and how much output the LLM is sending you back. There are, like, libraries called, TickToken. This is a very good
100xEngineers: way to do it, a quick math locally on your machine, or even, like, irrespective of whatever API you are using. So it's basically a fast tokenizer.
100xEngineers: It basically helps you to, like, calculate the number of tokens,
100xEngineers: They are open source tokenizer as well, which helps you to, like, do it for other models, but this is a good way what…
100xEngineers: you can do it. So you can ask Lot to install tick token, which means it counts each and every token which you are sending as an input, and then generating as an output. And that helps you to do an estimation of
100xEngineers: how much cost you're gonna bear per user from the token side of things. This is the request, which is how many requests you can make, but you also need to know how much tokens you are spending, because these are the two variables which will help you to estimate the unit economics per user. Now, in this case, let's say if
100xEngineers: the plan which we received, you can also do this,
100xEngineers: So I can take this entire plan, and I can use the… Let's say… when AI… tokenizer.
100xEngineers: There are tokenizers available, but this is a pretty standard one. Most of the tokenizers, like, use the same method. So I pasted the entire plan, it told me that it takes 451 token.
100xEngineers: So, this is the amount of token, and now I can just multiply this with whatever pricing I have for, let's say, Grok.
100xEngineers: Raw Cloud.
100xEngineers: Pricing.
100xEngineers: So, they have this on-demand pricing for all the models right now. Let's say we are using the Llama 3.1, this is…
100xEngineers: 0.005 per 20 million. So the amount what we spent is, like, barely nothing as compared to 20 million. So now you'll see that what I was telling you,
100xEngineers: Having clarity on which model to use and which platform to use plays a very important role in the overall costing.
100xEngineers: This easily can shoot up, to maybe, like, up to 10x more if I just use the Opus models right now in production, but because I'm using, let's say, something like Lama, the price would I pay…
100xEngineers: you can just, like, imagine, it's… it's barely, like, 000.1% of the… the actual cost, which I'll pay, for a dollar, right? So, which means, like, I can magnify this at least to…
100xEngineers: thousand, probably, like, 100,000 times, and then only I'll… I'll pay somewhere around $0.05, which is a pretty… pretty good deal for me, to be honest. And this is both for input and output, so… because input token are priced differently versus output. Output is what LLM produce, input is what you put into the LLM. So, usually, input cost is slightly lower.
100xEngineers: output is slightly higher. But in both of these cases, this is pretty cheap. So, for me, like, until I hit…
100xEngineers: $12.5 million and $20 million in those, I don't need to worry about it, because my cost is gonna be still under $0.5.
100xEngineers: So this is a great way for me to think about it as a unit economics course, which is something I want all of you to, as well, keep a note when you're building something like this.
100xEngineers: Another part here is about… now, as I said, like, this is what will help me to put a request or rate limit per user.
100xEngineers: maybe here I could say, Like, 10 requests per minute, and
100xEngineers: let's say 10K tokens, total number of tokens per…
100xEngineers: I think those limits were, I think, per day, if I'm not wrong, or maybe per… actually per request.
100xEngineers: Sorry.
100xEngineers: per day is actually too much. This is 10K…
100xEngineers: tokens per, per request, because I don't want to cap, like, say, all 20 millions to RF.
100xEngineers: So this allowed me to at least have 3 parallel users, which means that until when I can hit my free quota, I can still run this with 3 different users, and
100xEngineers: But after that, even if I put a paid plan, it's still gonna be, like, much lesser than, let's say, a dollar, if I have, like, even 200 people using it right now. So that's… that's one way of doing it, like, thinking about the overall cost.
100xEngineers: what this leads us is that now we need an identification and authentication system. Now, this is where the RF picture comes in. One of the easiest things which I can do is I can set up the
100xEngineers: Superbase Auth, because we already have a database. So, in the previous app… now, this is where I'll fall back to the previous version, because I don't have enough time left to start building it from scratch, but the method looks, like, exactly same, so…
100xEngineers: If I show you the database version which we built in the last class, I think I have…
100xEngineers: It tears.
100xEngineers: Yep.
100xEngineers: So this is the database which we built in the last class. We had the domain model. This is also what I recommend. Once you have done everything, just make sure you have clarity on domain model, because this will help you decide which kind of database you need to go for. I have chosen Superbase here, which is a Postgres SQL-type database, but you don't need to use that only for every single time. There are multiple other options.
100xEngineers: And as I said, like, I played the whole talk of decision-making and understanding how do you decide which database is better, which is the compilation of the lecture as well as the extension module of it. So, do refer to that.
100xEngineers: But use the same principles, create a domain models. This will help you to understand whether you need a relational database or static database, or non-relational. And in this case, I was able to find relationships between conversation and messages.
100xEngineers: the core idea was I have
100xEngineers: conversations and messages, and one more thing which now I can add, because I am… I'm having users, is that the authentication. So how does that look like is…
100xEngineers: I have these, one conversation and one authentication, one user.
100xEngineers: So, and then this is what ER diagrams looks like, which means that
100xEngineers: This is the one entity, and these are the attributes. Attributes are the… the text, which is the conversion text.
100xEngineers: And, in the messages, it's gonna be text, timestamp, so which is the role, user ID,
100xEngineers: And this is a primary key, this is a foreign key. So all of these things, something which I've already done, that's why I'm not repeating it, but
100xEngineers: The way how it works is super ways.
100xEngineers: starts the authentication on top of your existing module. One of the ways how I can show you, maybe from the existing demo, is that this is the project where we have
100xEngineers: the entities.
100xEngineers: from… Conversations and messages. These are two major entities we have. And…
100xEngineers: If I go back to the authentication part right now.
100xEngineers: You can see there are active users here, and one of the ways how you can use authentication is, is…
100xEngineers: I'll share…
100xEngineers: This whole doc, because this is a… this is a better way to start with, rather than…
100xEngineers: just prompting, as I said earlier, I mean, I was doing prompting for the concept that I've already taught you, because those are things which we have learned from first principles again. Now, if you're coming across with something new, like, there's also something that is new for us, right? Because we have not added this thing yet. So I would first recommend you to
100xEngineers: To do this, Like, learn the concepts about what is the authentication,
100xEngineers: what is the Superbase user? How does authentication work here? Because it's a managed solution. When I say managed, it means that something which is built and also completely end-to-end managed by the Superbase.
100xEngineers: There are another option, which is, like, you can build your own auth system, just like how you build our own backend. We can do that in the same way from First Principles.
100xEngineers: The only reason why I'm not willing to do it, because auth is something which is repetitive, it's the same problem every app has been facing, so…
100xEngineers: I would rather, like, use an existing out-of-the-shelf solution. This is also my thought process of bringing a third-party solution versus doing something in-house. The moment I have something which is core to my business logic, like, when I was doing the diagnosis tool, I don't want to delegate this to a third party, because then my entire business depends on that.
100xEngineers: So I will decide To build that in-house.
100xEngineers: even if that will take more effort and more money for me, because that is something proprietary to my knowledge. If tomorrow this app works for, say, 1,000, 2,000 people, I might want to defend that data. I don't want to share this data with everybody, a third-party vendor, so I… like, that's how most enterprises work, right? This is in the core IP. But something like the authentication, right, which is already managed.
100xEngineers: So the only thing which I'll be using here is the, all of the solutions, by the way, has to, like, do this, this thing, which is called personally identifiable information, which means that
100xEngineers: Anything which is,
100xEngineers: tied to a personally identifiable information, such as email ID, auth number, and things like that. Superbase…
100xEngineers: mask these things out. So nobody, including the developer of the database, or the developer, can see all these things, similar to, like, how we do hashing in password, which means that you'll encode the passwords and sensitive information
100xEngineers: in encrypted manner, in the database, but even accidentally a developer looks at the database values, just like I can look at the values of the messages right now, what I have here.
100xEngineers: So, this is exactly the same thing, by the way. Like, if a data… if a user who is sitting at Anthropyx
100xEngineers: Database, or managing it.
100xEngineers: they can actually look at the messages, and they can query things, and look at those things. But they cannot do the same thing with your password. They cannot do the same thing with your sensitive information, because there are laws around it, and they have to be compliant with it. And usually, the authentication is, like, something which is… which goes under those part. So I don't want to take on those… those headaches as well, like, building the whole compliances for it, and I'll rather use a third-party software.
100xEngineers: for it. And that's why I chose Superbase Auth for it.
100xEngineers: Multiple other options are available out there, like, you can use this. There's one more which I…
100xEngineers: to recommend, if somebody wants to try a new solution, this is called Clear.
100xEngineers: Both of them are good, actually. It's something which, if you use Hicksfield, and a lot of new companies are actually using even open router, things like that, which is… they give the whole UI as well, which just, like, looks like this, so you can install everything, including the UI components, including the whole, the backend of it, and everything is a third-party managed
100xEngineers: The clerk. So your clerk takes care of all the compliance as part of it, and you get
100xEngineers: this user management. So both of these options are available. Based on the need, you can choose that. I would…
100xEngineers: start with, first, the SuperPace authentication, and although I'm not gonna, like, write the code right now, but what I've done is, like, I've compiled all the steps in the
100xEngineers: the authentication table here, and I also, like, completed the same MVP, because I was…
100xEngineers: I was, like, thinking that if I won't be able to finish it, like, on time, I'll at least show you what is the overall output looks like. So this is one of the output, which… which actually does the front end.
100xEngineers: And, let me show you the front end first, because this is… I mean…
100xEngineers: So I'll go back to the same front-end which we have actually used. This is in the profile.
100xEngineers: The… if you remember the older one.
100xEngineers: And I'll also keep my backend up and running. This is my C7 MVP.
100xEngineers: The only one drawback here, which I can share is, especially with free server, is that this has a problem called cold start. So what it is facing and what it's doing right now is that whenever
100xEngineers: we have inactivity on the server, which is a free server on Ender. It will shut it down, which means that the computer and the machine which you… on which your code is running, it will either shut it down or reallocate this machine to someone else who is using it.
100xEngineers: Because Render wants to, like, do it efficiently and manage the free services so that they won't end up, like, I would say leaking money here.
100xEngineers: Which means a slight discomfort, that if there's an inactivity and then you want to use the app, so it takes, for example, right now it took almost, I think, 30-40 seconds to open up, but now the API is back.
100xEngineers: So I can now test it. So this is the deployed version, where I can… I can see this workflow diagnoster with me, and I can, like, mention my…
100xEngineers: Email?
100xEngineers: Let me see… 100xengineers.com.
100xEngineers: And, then I'll… the name, password… 1, 2, 3…
100xEngineers: So, the moment I added this password 123 and my email.
100xEngineers: It authenticated me, and the reason why it authenticated me is because this
100xEngineers: is enabled from this authentication on the database. So what you can do is you can come back to this authentication system, and I'll maybe, like, do it on the… just show it on the new account, if you are on, let's say, new project.
100xEngineers: You start a new project, let's say this is…
100xEngineers: test project, I'm gonna type in some name, some generate password.
100xEngineers: You're generating a new project here, so what you would need to do is, once the database is set up.
100xEngineers: go to the authentication, and the easiest way to do this is you can do the email authentication. So, there are, like, multiple providers here. As you can see, if you go to the sign-in providers, you are… you have phone number authentication, you have Web3 wallet, you have Apple, Azure, Bitpocket, Discord. So, Superbase gives you a lot of options to authenticate. So, which means that
100xEngineers: you can authenticate from… if somebody already has a Google account, they don't need to, like, type in the password. So, these all providers are out there. The only thing is you have to manually set up all of those things, and so, I would recommend, if you're testing it out, you just turn off the confirm email toggle, because otherwise it'll ask you to
100xEngineers: Confirm your email from… confirm your email account from…
100xEngineers: the code that it will send you, or the link it will send you on your email.
100xEngineers: So, it will become, like, slightly challenging, because Superbase has a limit here. The number of emails you can send on a free limit, free plan is limited, so you'll soon hit that limit.
100xEngineers: if you're testing and doing this while you're building the app, just turn this off. When you're in production, then you can turn it on. Just make sure that it is limited on a free plan, so you might need to upgrade
100xEngineers: to the premium tier, in order for you to get the authentication for this. If you don't want that, you can also choose something from there. Google has their authentication, which has a free limit, so you can set up it from Google as well. But this is the only setup which you need to do. Like, come to sign providers, allow new users, and
100xEngineers: The moment you do it, you can see this, let's say, yeah, so this is where, like, you have the authentication setup, and you will see this whole table, which is UID, display name, email, and phone number. Now, because we have only mentioned the email provider, so we only have email, but the moment you have more providers, it'll add all those things here. Superbase manages the entire authentication table.
100xEngineers: under users in the authentication tab. That's how it manages. So, I'll now go back and show you how it looks like for our app, the ROBS app. So, I've read the same thing.
100xEngineers: enable the email provider here, just, like, turned it off, and then I used the exact same demo in front of you, what I was using, from my account, Siddhanth 100X Engineers, and as you can see, like, I can also not…
100xEngineers: see any kind of password or any sensitive information here. So this is what, like, Superbase does by default. So what I can only see is the email,
100xEngineers: No.
100xEngineers: this email is linked to my whole app, so this is how the ER diagram today looks like, where everything, like, messages… so messages are connected to my conversations, and conversations have, I would say.
100xEngineers: each and every authenticated user. So, only after creating an account, after doing a sign-up from email and password, you can create an auth ID, which is auth user ID, and that is the route for creating a conversation, which means now, as compared to the previous version which we initially built.
100xEngineers: during this whole sprint, where anyone can create any number of requests. Now, every member is capped on how many conversations plus how many messages they can send, because I can check, hey, how many messages Arav has sent. So I can always go back to my table editor, and I can see that all of these messages
100xEngineers: Are now linked to something called
100xEngineers: conversation ID, and conversation ID, which is the foreign key in the messages table, is linked to user ID. So right now, like, I've not created it. Let me create one conversation here. Let's see if I can…
100xEngineers: put the same…
100xEngineers: So let me put it here, and
100xEngineers: Okay, it gave me the answer, and actually this time it gave me a much better answer. It sounds like you're starting a manual process, this is the repeatable steps, automation opportunities, and it also gave me a code, by the way, so it's, like, actually a very good response, which we got from the workflow diagnoser.
100xEngineers: and MVP project. Now, let me confirm with my database, if I got something here or not.
100xEngineers: So, I got my first…
100xEngineers: user ID linked message, or conversation here. So the same message or conversation which I opened, because now, this time, in the older ones, I was testing without user, so hence, this ID was null, but the conversation which I just sent in front of you guys, this one.
100xEngineers: it is linked to my user ID, which I can track from this, and now I can see that
100xEngineers: who is this user ID, who is this authentication user? So I can always find this user, and it is authenticated, and the email is Sidhant. So every single conversation is now tied to this particular user.
100xEngineers: And now I can keep a cap that, hey, I can now go back to my, I would say, whole logic of writing this. And this is… this is where, like, things get interesting, where you… you start
100xEngineers: like, writing the caps for it, and… and this is also, like, what it looks like when you start planning to deploy this app in front of people, so you know how much your unit cost is, which we just learned how to calculate, by understanding the technology, what you're using, and the input and output tokens.
100xEngineers: And then, like, putting a cap and applying the same thing here. There are, like, a couple of more concepts which I…
100xEngineers: haven't yet covered, but as I said, like, this is… this is the main journey which I want to walk it through in the live, so that everybody who is here on this call at least have the same clarity. One more thing which I'll do is I'll… the part which I was not able to, like, build live, I'll try to document it. Maybe I'll share some videos as well, pre-recorded ones, by next week.
100xEngineers: Which you can follow along, similar to what we did with the Level 1 and Level 2 stack, if you have followed around that series.
100xEngineers: Which will…
100xEngineers: show you these… these things, like, adding this particular part, the authentication, the… the, anything which is, like, on top of it and beyond of this particular, section. How do you…
100xEngineers: do that.
100xEngineers: But that was, like, a whole point, so I hope…
100xEngineers: this… this was something which is useful, and I hope you get at least a clear idea of
100xEngineers: how you can do something like this, maybe in 2 to 3 hours. Ideally, it should not take more than 3 hours to do and to build this entire thing live. Because I was live explaining and I was talking a lot, if I just sit down and be quiet, I think I can work much more faster.
100xEngineers: So, what I'll do as a part of this, I'll also share all the templates, all the repositories, the super-based terms, so you guys can, like, follow along with that. And that's basically the end of this session.
100xEngineers: If you have any questions about anything which we discussed, you can let me know in the chat. If you don't have any questions, don't drop off right now. I have to share the announcement about the hackathon. Your hackathon will start exactly at 10pm today. So, although we'll send everything in the written format as well, but I still, like.
100xEngineers: Share some information, and officially, like, hand over you guys the problem statements.
100xEngineers: But before that, if you have any questions or any doubts about everything which I did, I know I did a lot of things today, so you can let me know in the chat.
100xEngineers: Yeah, you know, economics is one of the most important things, Shefali. I can tell you because I spent and wasted a lot of money here.
100xEngineers: I can actually give you more examples, in the written guide, maybe in the recorded guides. So, yeah, I think that's something which is, as a practice side, also something which you guys can do. Even the problem statement, I would say you guys will end up solving during the hackathon.
100xEngineers: do think about the unit economics first, even in the beginning stage, I would say. Like, the only thing which you need is that input-output pairs, as I said. And the moment you have your first function, which
100xEngineers: In this case, we started the code business logic written. I would say right after that, you can start calculating your unit economics cost. That's actually, like, a much better way to do it.
100xEngineers: So the only thing which, Indira, you need for the hackathon is all the lectures beyond this. As I said, like, even… even this lecture, I think the only thing which I have mentioned are these things, which is the last bit.
100xEngineers: Zoom takes…
100xEngineers: two to… sometimes, like, two and a half hours to send us the recording and, like, give us the transcript. So, expect the delay of, like, two hours. That's what we initially thought. So, hence, like, 10PM is what we have, mentioned, the hackathon timeline. So, hopefully, by the end of 10PM,
100xEngineers: will get the recordings of this lecture as well, and you'll be receiving everything live on the LMS, along with this lecture, as well as the notes. But I think everything, apart from this, is something which is already uploaded, including the database guide, which I was mentioning, and also the previous lectures and the notes we had.
100xEngineers: the GitHub repositories are something which I uploaded. If not, like, I'll reshare it on the Discord immediately after this call, so that anyone who wants to follow along with the GitHub that we have built as a part of the code, you guys can do that. So you can find this under the resources channel on Discord channel.
100xEngineers: The hackathon will end in exactly 24 hours. This hackathon is a short one, this short sprint hackathon, because we realized that there are a lot of people who are not available throughout the weekend, and it won't be fair for us to, like, do it, like, separately for some people, and…
100xEngineers: like, differently for other people. So we are sticking to the 24-hour
100xEngineers: timeline. The next hackathon, and this, you know, this is also, like, I would say a pre…
100xEngineers: what do you say, like a warm-up kind of thing? Like, for a bigger hackathon. In my journey, like, I have planned a bigger hackathon for you guys at the end of the Module 2. Now, because we are not at the completion of Module 2,
100xEngineers: So the reason why I want to do a hackathon right now is so that you guys are prepared for it, because in the bigger ones, you won't have the same time, and some of the things which you will learn in this one are definitely gonna be worth, I would say.
100xEngineers: things that… that you can apply in the main one. That is the, I would say, the… the, hackathon, which… which is, like, serious, and you can actually get some serious incentives also in that one. So there are two hackathons in this cohort. One is happening, like, right now, tomorrow. It's gonna last for 24 hours.
100xEngineers: So, you can see the deadline for… start from 10…
100xEngineers: PM tonight, and it'll end at 10 p.m. tomorrow night, ISD.
100xEngineers: So you get 24 hours. The problems are scoped in that way as well, so it's not something which you need to solve, and it will take you, I would say, a couple of days.
100xEngineers: One of the reasons why I wanted to do this specific lecture right now is because you will see that amount of time, amount of thinking, and the decision-making it takes for you to go from an idea to app, once you have done your observation and hypothesis working, which was, like, I think pretty much, like.
100xEngineers: on point, right? I think you guys can follow the same playbook. So for… for you, I think it would be less than…
100xEngineers: maybe, like, 3 to 4 hours, which I'm expecting, even if you're a beginner, you have to, like, refer to the videos. I think it should not take you more than 3 to 4 hours, if you're building the first MVP version of it.
100xEngineers: Yeah, so that's… that's what the expectation is, but do go through the brief. I'll share the brief with all of you, and we'll give you some overview as well.
100xEngineers: But yeah.
100xEngineers: What are the rules of the hackathon? As I said, I'll share that. Yeah, we'll share all the details. We have the whole guidebook wishlist. So, in fact, I would request my team, because at this point, I think we have finished the lecture content, so you can make the guidebook
100xEngineers: available to everybody. Let me see if I can also… Access it.
100xEngineers: You don't need to do it individually… sorry, in a collaboration, Aniroth. This hackathon is… 24-hour hackathon is an individual hackathon, so you don't need to make teams or form teams. The moment you receive the problem statement, you can start working on it. Every submission is going to be an individual submission.
100xEngineers: That's how we're gonna market as well.
100xEngineers: You need to definitely complete the MVP version of it, Gio.
100xEngineers: So… I have mentioned the exact specifics in the… document.
100xEngineers: And the way how you will get to know whether this is an MVP, which is a viable product, is because you will get the feedback from your peers. So, if you have built an MVP, which means it's a viable product, but minimal yet, which means it doesn't have the fancy UI, doesn't still have… like, even if a Gradio app works, a Streamlit app works, but it has to solve a problem. Just like this app.
100xEngineers: The output it gave me, like.
100xEngineers: it should actually help RF, the output which we basically saw. That is a more important part. So the reason why I also spent more time in the first half of this call in just, like, doing that, thinking around what should be the business logic.
100xEngineers: and how I should solve that, that is also the approach which I would recommend you. So, spend more time there. It's okay to have an ugly UI, but a very good solution, or a good plan, output coming from the app.
100xEngineers: Versus, like, having a very fancy UI, but not a valuable output. So that is the… that is how you should focus on. But yeah, it needs to be a valuable output year. So that's how we want to judge it.
100xEngineers: Yes, you can start at late night, you can start at any given point of time. Starting is not a problem. Submission needs to be on time, Yasir. So, submission needs to be on time, which is 10 PM tomorrow IST.
100xEngineers: Okay, so this is the time to reveal the problem statements. Let me… Just make sure I'm…
100xEngineers: I'm dropping the link, and this is your problem statement link. You will have
100xEngineers: 1 hour, 15 minutes of buffer time before the problem statement and the official hackathon kicks off. So this is the time which you can take to look at the problem statement. I'll give you a quick brief. As I said, it'll start at 10pm IST, Friday 19 June.
100xEngineers: 10PM ISG, Saturday, 20 June is the deadline. No submission will be accepted beyond that, so just make sure you start at any time, but submit it on time.
100xEngineers: There are 3 problem statements, which means 3 things you can choose from.
100xEngineers: In this document, it's mentioned as three tracks.
100xEngineers: everything has to be done solo, individual. There is no group effort which is involved here in terms of building it. Definitely, when you start evaluating the problem statement, you need the help of different users, which you can use. Maybe you can ask your peers. The…
100xEngineers: no-code group is right now not having any hackathon. So you have, like, a set of peers who are available, who are not participating in a hackathon, who don't have the same competitive
100xEngineers: angle towards you. So I would say, like, you can… you can make some friends as well during this hackathon. So do talk to people, do, like, try to recruit them, and…
100xEngineers: get the validation from the users, especially people who are not your direct competitors. So that's also a very strategic decision which we took, so that we have at least half of the cohort which is not participating in the hackathon, and half of the cohort is participating. So the people who are participating right now are the CodeTrack folks. All of you will be
100xEngineers: Doing it individually.
100xEngineers: All the comms are gonna happen on Discord.
100xEngineers: We'll have a live sync tomorrow with our mentor, so…
100xEngineers: Every 6 hours, we're gonna do a check-in, which means that
100xEngineers: starting from today, like, starting from 10, the next time we do it, we'll send an automatic message on the Discord. You have to post your check-in, which means the progress. What are the to-dos? What are the things that you have done? What are the blockers, if you have any blockers?
100xEngineers: Or, what is the next step for you? So that our team can monitor
100xEngineers: that how many of you are making progress. And if somebody is genuinely stuck because of a problem, which is something that we can help you, not related to giving you a solution, but maybe some operational help, then we'll basically look into it. But again, no commitment towards it, that
100xEngineers: This is… because it's a competition, not…
100xEngineers: a lecture or somebody who is doing an assignment. So the… the… I would say the environment is designed in such a way that you will feel that competitive vibe, and there'll be very little help you can expect right now from especially the solutioning part of it. Even the mentors, I have instructed them to not give you any hints or anything like that.
100xEngineers: This is the part which you need to do on your own.
100xEngineers: And this is where you will also start, maybe, putting your mind muscles. Coming back to the three problem statements, there are some gotchas about this handbook, how you can use it, and everything about the hackathon problem statements. I would say take your time, read out everything, but I'll quickly give you a walkthrough of the… the three problem statements. This is the…
100xEngineers: The one?
100xEngineers: The first one is the concept check, the second one is the eval co-pilot, third one is the EI bottleneck diagnostic.
100xEngineers: The way how we have designed the problem statement is…
100xEngineers: that all of this are something which you can use as the student of 100x Engineers, which was not a convenience, but a very deliberate move.
100xEngineers: To make it effective.
100xEngineers: and make it human-led, rather than you generating an AI slop.
100xEngineers: I'm very much aware that
100xEngineers: every single person can take all these briefs and put it into Cloud, or GPT, or wherever you have your AI model, and generate a plausible solution which looks like a solution that something… someone has actually built.
100xEngineers: But we have made all the measures, and because I've done this cohort seven times, and I've seen, like, how people cheat, and how people, like, also learn, so both of the things are there. Like, the focus of this problem statement is to make you learn, rather than just, like, giving you
100xEngineers: an opportunity to just paste everything into AI and then get the answer back from it.
100xEngineers: So how we have done that is, we have first
100xEngineers: Asked you that minimum criteria for submission.
100xEngineers: whether you choose track A, B, C, which means any problem statement, you have to validate it with at least two users, which means that if you solve, let's say, problem number one, and the problem number one is
100xEngineers: In a very brief manner, it's basically building a tool
100xEngineers: that tells a learner whether they truly understand a concept, or whether they only recognize the words for it. And this is a very common problem which I see among a lot of people, so it could be helpful for you as well.
100xEngineers: So you pointed at a systems thinking concept, let's say you ask a question about interface, API, front-end, back-end, and
100xEngineers: this tool…
100xEngineers: Now, whether you want to use LLM, whether you want to use a different system, that's completely up to you. As I said, like, no recommendation about system here. The only thing which we have mentioned is about the problem. So…
100xEngineers: You'd need to design a system that can… Help a learner
100xEngineers: To know whether they have understood a concept fully or not, or whether they only just…
100xEngineers: Lo- like, have learned the…
100xEngineers: definition of it, or maybe facts about it. Now, how will you do that? There's a whole document which I've written, so it'll help you to guide towards it.
100xEngineers: by asking you the questions in a Socratic manner.
100xEngineers: So it finds one place of explanation, stops, where you need to understand where the person or the student
100xEngineers: has stopped the understanding thing… understanding process, and started just, like, memorizing things. So, this is the whole process of this tool. Now, the best part, as I said, is it can be used across
100xEngineers: All 250 people who have joined this cohort.
100xEngineers: Including the alumnis of 100x Engineers. So you are open to talk to alumnis as well, you're open to talk to the current cohort students, but the minimum requirement for you to submit any of these form statements, track A, track B, track C, is that you need to validate it with at least two people, which means there needs to be
100xEngineers: two people who are not your immediate friends, not your, I would say, family members, or somebody who is, like, working with you very closely. They are the two people who needs to be part of the cohort, either this cohort or the previous cohort.
100xEngineers: And they should give you the output. They should give you the validation that, hey.
100xEngineers: Yes, I was able to, like, find a way that this particular concept, which I was not able to understand, when I used your tool, I was able to do that. So this is how we're gonna, like, monitor it, which is gonna be difficult to fake, because you have to, like, at some point, use the human interaction.
100xEngineers: It has been designed in that way. The second one is about the eval co-pilot, which is…
100xEngineers: about building a solution for understanding what good looks like. A very core part of the lecture itself, what I took, because I was…
100xEngineers: as kind of, like, I would say, immune to now looking at apps without a good evaluation system, and sometimes even I don't know what is a good looks like for each and everything. So it's a problem.
100xEngineers: Now, how do we solve this problem? It's a part of the challenge. Like, can you build something like this? Can you build a solution where
100xEngineers: Let's say a fellow builder, fellow cohort batchmates, they can put in their project, let's say whatever they have built.
100xEngineers: And, this will help them to first write the golden set of rubrics.
100xEngineers: for their own AI feature, let's say the diagnose function that we have built, we have used Claude for that, by the way, to write the eval prompt, but can it
100xEngineers: can this thing do a better job than what a generic Claude prompt can do? Because I can tell you right now, the Claude prompt which it wrote for me, it's not the best one, right? And it can be improved. So, how do you build this? This is more like an understanding how evals work from the principles, and like, if you solve this problem, I think you understand evals really well.
100xEngineers: And you can, like, also, like, help other people to build evals for them.
100xEngineers: The TRACC, which is the third problem statement, is about the AI bottleneck diagnostic, very similar to the RF's problem statement, but there's a very
100xEngineers: I would say a specific nuance here. The nuance is that this works for
100xEngineers: people who are also, I'd say, part of your cohort, and they are, like, on a journey with you.
100xEngineers: let's say they are building something. They are not like Arav, because Arav's persona is more like the same version of 100x Engineers cohort students who were before joining the program. Like, when they didn't join the program, they were thinking about joining it, because that was the pre,
100xEngineers: Of, like, this whole experiment. So this is slightly different in terms of the… the state.
100xEngineers: The people who are working with you, they have problem statements, they have learned the projects, they have learned the concepts.
100xEngineers: Now, their bottlenecks could be different. They are not at the same stage where RF is, which means that they are not just figuring out how to build a workflow. If you build something like this, the same thing which I built is not going to be qualified for this problem statement, because something that I already told you. Your job is, can you do a better job than this, which means
100xEngineers: if I give your solution, if you solve this as part of the track theory, which is the third problem statement, if I give this to any person in the cohort randomly.
100xEngineers: Can they use this solution and understand what is the bottleneck for them? Why they're not being able to solve a particular step where they are stuck? Because I can give you a guarantee that every single person
100xEngineers: At least at any given point of time in this cohort, have found
100xEngineers: One thing where they got stuck.
100xEngineers: Or they're not able to move past.
100xEngineers: And sometimes it takes a mentor, sometimes it takes a human, sometimes it takes AI, sometimes it takes mixer hauler to understand what is the bottleneck, because you have your blind spots, everyone has their own blind spots, so we can't understand this thing. So this actually becomes another very important tool that you yourself can use throughout the cohort. Like, if you end up building it, it would be helpful for you
100xEngineers: for the rest of the cohort, that you can use a diagnostic tool to understand it. Again, how you solve it, that's a part of the problem statement. Like, how do you find a solution that can not only just diagnose the workflow.
100xEngineers: from a workflow description, but can diagnose the bottleneck that why, let's say, Yasiri is not able to build a solution after implementing and deploying his APIs on Render, and what is the bottleneck exactly he's facing, which even he himself is not able to articulate well.
100xEngineers: So, these are the three problem statement themes.
100xEngineers: what you can do is, here we have mentioned about the checkpoints and 24-hour clock, what will happen. This is… the briefing is, like, done. What I'll do is I won't take too much of your time.
100xEngineers: First thing I would recommend you is make sure you create a plan.
100xEngineers: read the problem statements. This is designed in such a way which is very Socratic, which will force you to think, and the goal of this entire hackathon is to just
100xEngineers: activate your thinking muscles, your prefrontal cortex. So try not to use AI for everything.
100xEngineers: I have mentioned exactly the points and places where you need to write the hand-drawn diagrams and hand-drawn visuals, so you need to follow that. If somebody is not following it, they will basically get deductions in their overall submissions, so…
100xEngineers: The first thing is, go through this.
100xEngineers: it will ask you, like, all the questions, force you to think about things. Once you have clarity on which track you want to choose, make sure you… you mention the track.
100xEngineers: early on in the Discord channel itself. So submit by 10pm, submit your pick track on Discord, mention it.
100xEngineers: 4AM will send you a notification for the first check-in. Now, it's optional, you don't need to be awake at that time, but it's the first check-in, especially people who are in a different time zone, maybe you can send your first check-in there, status update. But whenever you wake up next time, like, which is…
100xEngineers: Let's say when you sleep today, and then you wake up tomorrow.
100xEngineers: do send your first check-in. Second check-in will send at 10 a.m. tomorrow morning.
100xEngineers: These are check-ins where you need to send your updates. These are mandatory check-ins. This is also what helps us to understand what was your progress throughout the 24 hours. Did you accidentally just came up with an idea 2 hours ago and pushed everything? If that, then we'll be very skeptical and we'll try to, like, understand whether you have done it wisely or not, because we want to see the whole journey. The point is not to just submit things, but
100xEngineers: To see, like, how you have evolved from an idea, initially what you thought could be a solution, but then it changed and evolved and pivoted into things. So it has to go through this forward check-in process, so make sure you send us the update. This is a part of the evaluation as well.
100xEngineers: The third check-in would be at 4pm, and then final check-in would be at 9pm night, and 10 is where we close all the submissions.
100xEngineers: as I said, now I won't take too much time, because at 10 exactly, we'll start the…
100xEngineers: hackathon. So, everything what you need to know is mentioned in this doc.
100xEngineers: I would say take your time. The next one hour is just about you understanding the problem statement, looking at it, working, and deciding it. Don't need to start work in the next one hour. Take this one hour to read the document, to select the problem statement. Three problem statements, you pick one. If you have any questions, the burning questions right now, I'll just quickly take that, and then we'll basically sign off from this, and you guys can focus on this
100xEngineers: Hackathon.
100xEngineers: Just make sure you mention your time zone. Yes, so you… our team will be… be able to track, like, let's say if somebody is at a different time zone, and you want to, like, you're starting late, or you're starting early, so do mention that time zone where you're operating.
100xEngineers: Will there be winners at the end? Yes, definitely, Manish. There'll be winners at the end. We have some special incentives.
100xEngineers: For the winners as well.
100xEngineers: try to submit the tracks before the first check-in. That's the final deadline which I can share with everybody.
100xEngineers: So, if you are somebody who is in a different time zone, maybe you want to take some time off, or maybe you want to
100xEngineers: You have, say, something which is… you cannot, like, lock the track the next 1 hour.
100xEngineers: Before we do the first check-in, which is the 4 AM ISD.
100xEngineers: Make sure you finalize your track. Ideally, everybody should do this by 10pm.
100xEngineers: Like, if you can.
100xEngineers: recommendation is lock the track by 10PM, but this is the point where, beyond this,
100xEngineers: Like, will not be able to, like…
100xEngineers: help you lock in the problem statement, because then it'll be, like, too confusing for you in the next day. Because if you keep switching the problem statement, it's anyways less time for you to, like, work on one thing, and if you keep switching it, then it'll become even less and chaotic for you as well as for us.
100xEngineers: And you won't be able to evaluate whether you have done, like, a good job or not. So, before the first check-in, which is 4AM IST,
100xEngineers: Just make sure you do it. It's the deadline, but recommendation is 10PM, if you can do it within the next 1 hour.
100xEngineers: You don't need to find people from previous cohort, Yasir, what I was saying, that it has to be the users of this
100xEngineers: cohort, or this, problem statement, needs to become from 100x engineers, because these are the primary people who have faced these problems, what I have mentioned. So…
100xEngineers: It's either and or. You can also take interviews from the current cohort, C7,
100xEngineers: If you also have access to somebody from C6, C4, C5, you can also do that. Given the user or the person is part of the 100xNGS cohort, you can take interviews, and their validation will be counted toward the submission.
100xEngineers: That's a clarification.
100xEngineers: No, not all the tracks needs to be built for him. So, if you mean that tracks with the code and no-code track, so then the only code track which we need to… who is doing this right now, no-code will do the hackathon next week.
100xEngineers: Among these three, you have to pick one. You don't need to do all three. You need to pick one.
100xEngineers: Yes, Yasir.
100xEngineers: Any concept that you have learned.
100xEngineers: In general, I would rather focus, you to test this with a concept that you have learned in the last 2-3 months, so that you can find people easily, and they can also, like, give you feedback that, hey, whether this one was able to help me gather the insight, whether I understood interface or not, or API or not.
100xEngineers: Resnick, we have mentioned the submission criteria, so I would say, like, just, like, you can go through the doc, and submission criteria is written there. So this is the submission criteria for… a submission template for each and every problem statement. So this is for everything what we have mentioned.
100xEngineers: You need to send the concepts you have tested. This is the first problem statement. Along with the public GitHub repolling, make sure your GitHub is accessible, only then we can evaluate it.
100xEngineers: You can use the links
100xEngineers: or screenshot of the people who you are doing the interviews. You can also maybe ask them to record a video, you can ask them to send a screenshot, but it has to be an evidence which we can back.
100xEngineers: just by sharing the Discord ID won't help us. So you can just go through the whole thing, right? Because we need to make sure that you have actually spoken to people. So if you have asked somebody to take an interview, just tell them that, hey, I might need to send this information to 100x Team as part of the proof. So, although most of the people are okay with that, but…
100xEngineers: If not, at least you should be… you should be, I'd say, set the expectations clearly, that the conversation that you are doing for the validation of this product is something that we need to record. Either you can do voice recording, video recording, screenshot, all of these things, which help us to validate whether you have… so…
100xEngineers: Yeah, that's something which is modern. So not only Discord ID will help.
100xEngineers: But, just go through it, and I think,
100xEngineers: Yes, yes, you can get the validation of no-code user, definitely.
100xEngineers: That's what I said.
100xEngineers: And I didn't say you should not use AI, just to be clear that I know everybody can use AI, and there is no way for me to identify when and how much you have used AI.
100xEngineers: The only thing here is that you have to solve the problem and be honest with the process, because the whole process is not about just submitting things, as I said. It's about, like, learning
100xEngineers: How to solve the problems.
100xEngineers: So there are ways, again, you can accelerate your journey, but just make sure you do the…
100xEngineers: validation with real human beings, because that's where you will learn. Make sure you write the hypothesis by your hand. So I've mentioned that
100xEngineers: design the system.
100xEngineers: diagrams, and do this by hand. Don't use AI for this. Don't use, I would say, any fancy tool for this. Try to do the basic pen, paper, design the system design, design, the domain model.
100xEngineers: All of these things, maybe write your hypothesis also on hand, but these are the two things which are mandatory. We need the hand-drawn diagrams from you.
100xEngineers: Okay, I think at this point, anyone who is…
100xEngineers: curious. I think you can go through the doc. If you still have more questions, you can let me know in the WhatsApp. Our team will be active until the next, one hour before we start, officially the kickoff, so you will be answering the questions.
100xEngineers: And, I wish you all the best, guys. I think this is the time where you start testing what you have learned, and hopefully this experience will also teach you something… something interesting. But until then.
100xEngineers: I'll say goodnight, and wish you all the best. Bye-bye. I'll share all the links, by the way, in the Discord, Manish.
100xEngineers: So, see you!